{"question_id": "Tx39GCUOS5AYAFK", "question_text": "does this work with cisco ip phone 7942", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Use the Plantronics compatibility guide to see what is compatible with your phone. http://www.plantronics.com/us/compatibility-guide/"}, {"answer_text": "I think that you will need a extra cord, but, To avoid offering you any false information,   We highly recommend contacting the manufacturer of this product for more specific information.   if you are not sure about it, you can go first to :  http://www.plantronics.com/us/support/  or call Plantronics TOLL FREE SUPPORT: 1-855-765-7878 24-HOUR SUPPORT SUNDAY 2PM-FRIDAY 5PM (PT)  they will answer all the questions you need to know about it."}, {"answer_text": "I'm really not positive. It works with our phones that include model numbers 7941, 7945 and 7961."}]}
{"question_id": "TxH4TPAQFBLE5L", "question_text": "Is this compatible with the cisco ip phone 7970 / 7961 models?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Don\u2019t know. Call Plantronics"}, {"answer_text": "Well...Don't know."}, {"answer_text": "This headset should work but it requires a separate adapter to go with it in order too connect with this telephone. Below is a headset that includes the cord you'll need to connect with your Cisco phones.  https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MYGZGUV"}, {"answer_text": "Hello! Yes it is compatible, however please note you will need an adapter cable in order to plug it into the phone. The model of the cable depends on the phone that you have. The compatible model for both phones is a U10 cable, Part Number: 26716-01. Feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815 if you have any other questions!"}]}
{"question_id": "TxQE5FTUZUKZTX", "question_text": "If i have a polycom vvx, what adapter cable will i need to plug in this headset to?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi Gabrielle, what is the model of VVX?"}, {"answer_text": "This head set come with its own cable"}, {"answer_text": "Plantronics 27190-01 QD/ED to RJ-9  See...  http://support.polycom.com/global/documents/support/technical/products/voice/FP37477 Using Headsets With Polycom Phones.pdf"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3G6XE2PTGUTHY", "question_text": "Does this headset work with a samsung galaxy s6 edge cell phone? if so, which adapter does it require? is that adapter available on amazon?  thanks.", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "no wont work"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx29KTO6BDODB6F", "question_text": "Will this work for a polycom vvx phone? also, is it necessary to purchase that extra adapter if i will use only with ploycom?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes, but you need a cable in between the headset and the Polycom. Plantronics Part Number: 27190-01"}, {"answer_text": "Hi there, yes this headset will work with your Polycom phone but you'll need to purchase the U10P direct connect cable as well. Out of the box this headset won't connect to anything unless you purchase the adapter for specific phones. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions."}, {"answer_text": "Per Polycom: These are compatible headsets for Polycom Soundpoint IP 300, 301, 335, 430, 450, 500, 501, 550, 560, 600, 601, 650, 670, CX300, CX500, CX600, CX700, VVX 101, VVX 201, VVX 300, 301, VVX 310, 311, VVX 400, 401, VVX 410, 411, VVX 500, 501, VVX 600, 601, VVX 1500.  Plantronics Corded Headsets: Only the Plantronics  SupraPlus \" (HW251, HW251N, HW261, HW261N),  \"EncorePro 500 series \" (HW530, HW540) and the  \"EncorePro 700 series \" (HW710, HW720) are compatible + Plantronics U10P Cable (part# 27190-01). All the other models may cause a buzzing sound in the headset. Or pick from any one of the pre-packaged Polycom certified headsets (part# ends with -POLY) below. Note: corded headset solution above require 2 pieces - the headset and the RJ-9 bottom cable.\""}, {"answer_text": "Pls call Polycom"}, {"answer_text": "yes, you will need the extra cable"}]}
{"question_id": "TxR5E9R4A6QSII", "question_text": "When you use the mute button can the person on the other end hear you putting them on mute?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hello, the answer is no, the other person cannot hear when you are putting them on mute. :) please call 1800-683-5715 for any further questions. Thanks"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2MH61M1HRNMZM", "question_text": "will this work with cisco 7942 phone? what cable i need to buy??", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "I would call Headsets.com in San Francisco.   They are will know.  I buy my other supplies from them  800-432-3738"}, {"answer_text": "Hi Libin, you will need the U10 direct connect cable, part number  26716-01. Give us a call with any further questions at 1-800-683-5715."}]}
{"question_id": "TxKFNX4GCQETFN", "question_text": "Is there a connector that will work with a Blackberry and /or an iPhone?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "I don't think so.  It connects with a regular phone type plug."}, {"answer_text": "i don't know if it has a connector. i bought for our work phones Avaya."}, {"answer_text": "No, this isn't meant to use with a cell phone."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx24LVV77BBWB6", "question_text": "Does it come with a 2.5mm jack ?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "It does not. We had to purchase the DA40 USB Digital Adapter to work with our VVX-500 phones. Part # 71800-41"}, {"answer_text": "no, it never does. Comes with a Quick Disconnect socket.  However, we sell a  short cable ($6.95) that has a 3.5mm pin on one end and a quick discocnnect socket  on the other that might connect this headset to your device (unsure).  Call Plantronics to find out if these 2 items might work on oyur make and model of device"}, {"answer_text": "No, that would need to be purchased separately."}, {"answer_text": "No it does not. It has the Plantronics Quick Disconnect (QD) connector which must be used with a proper adapter cable."}, {"answer_text": "No, it does not."}, {"answer_text": "I don't know the answer to this, but when we purchased our equipment we called Plantronics directly.  They were completely helpful, answered our questions and didn't try to sell us more than we needed."}, {"answer_text": "Yes, I believe so"}]}
{"question_id": "TxJPTVTNQ4NV60", "question_text": "Which cord do i need to connect this to a polycom vvx600?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi there, you would need the U10P 27190-01 direct connect cable. Another model to consider is the Discover D701 and you would need the D100 direct connect cable with that. Below is a link for your reference and give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions. https://www.amazon.com/Discover-D701-Single-Office-Headset/dp/B01GGRAOYW/ref sr 1 1?ie UTF8&qid 1480543290&sr 8-1&keywords discover+d701"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3HZ0F6NFTPC2Y", "question_text": "Bought this for an iphone 6, what type of adapter do I need to plug into phone?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi Heather, you will need the QD-3.5mm adapter. Below is a link for you. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions. http://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-Cable-Assy-Right-Angle/dp/B000COKYXM/ref sr 1 1?ie UTF8&qid 1463666726&sr 8-1&keywords plantronics+qd-3.5mm"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2HP4VG0P0G8X3", "question_text": "does it work with Lucent 6416D", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "I'm not sure.  I used it to plug in to my computer for use with the Vonage soft phone.  It worked great in my use case.  I'm sorry I couldn't be of more assistance."}, {"answer_text": "It depends...On all of the 6400 Series telephones except the 6416D+M and 6424D+M, the headset connection consists of a headpiece and modular base unit.  The handset plugs into the modular base unit, the headset with A10 Connector plugs into the modular base unit as well.    If you have the 6416D+M and 6424D+M sets, there is a jack provided for ONLY the headset. On these sets, the headset can either be connected with an adapter cord (the Plantronics A10 Connector) to the Headset jack on the back of the telephone or connected to a modular base unit which then plugs into the Headset jack.    Refer to the manual for diagrams: http://www.beatriceco.com/bti/porticus/bell/pdf/bsp/555230739 avaya  6408d+ users guide.pdf"}, {"answer_text": "I'm not sure, I ordered it for a friend who works in a telecommunication company."}, {"answer_text": "I have only used Cisco phone with this product. Call plantronics 1 888 752 6876."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3TU75AOGLQPCF", "question_text": "Can I use this with a Polycom phone?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes, you will also need the following interface cable below. Thank you.    https://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-Polaris-Headset-Disconnect-2719001/dp/B00006B7RS/ref sr 1 1?s office-products&ie UTF8&qid 1542307398&sr 1-1&keywords 27190-01"}, {"answer_text": "Hello! Yes, you can use a HW251N headset as long as your using the correct adapter cable. In most cases Polycom phones require a U10P cable (PN: 27190-01). We suggest you to confirm this by checking our Compatibility guide available online or contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815 for further assistance!"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx241Y3CJH5F22A", "question_text": "Does it work with a Cisco phone/system? thanks!", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hello, the HW251N has an open ended connection called a QD, which makes it compatible with different devices. In this case we would need your phone's specific model to check this. You can also find the compatibility guide directly on our official website under Support   Tools. If you have any other questions, please don't hesitate to contact Plantronics Customer Care at 800-985-9815."}, {"answer_text": "Yes but you'll need an adapter to go with it in order to plug into your Cisco phone. The headset at the link below comes included with this cable. 1-800-683-5715  https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MYGZGUV"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx36WO17L2VRD8N", "question_text": "I have a vvx311 polycom phone and would like to buy the supra plus hw251n headset.  do i need to purchase anything else to go along with it?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi! Yes. According to our Compatibility Guide, you will need to use the U10P quick disconnect cable in order to connect the headset to your desk phone. Please feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance."}, {"answer_text": "Yes you would need a direct connect cable to go with the headset that's sold separate or you can get the headset at the link below that will include that cable. 1-800-683-5715  https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01MYGZGUV?ref myi title dp"}]}
{"question_id": "TxH0WDHBQUQDQH", "question_text": "Will this work with my comdial impact phone, and if so do i need to purchase anything else?  i do not need wireless system.", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "You'll need an M22 amplifier too, and the quick-disconnect cord that goes with it. This HW251N won't plug directly into your comdial."}, {"answer_text": "According to Plantronics, the following are compatible. Impact DXP, FX: 8012, 8101, 8112, 8124, 8024S (Use Aux Jack, Enable headet mode) Impact SCS: 8201, 8212, 8312, 8324, 8412, 8425 (Use Aux Jack, Enable headet mode)"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1YJLNU0Y8SX9B", "question_text": "will this work with avaya phone 9611g model?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hello! Yes, it is compatible with your Avaya phone  however, in order to be able to connect your headset you require either an M22 amplifier  or you can use quick disconnect cable called HIS cord. The part number for this cable is: 72442-41. If you have any further questions, please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team: 800-985-9815."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2IQ8TV6J02WYW", "question_text": "Is there a way to remove the headset that goes over the head and use an adapter to over the ear instead?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hello! No, this version is not convertible. We recommend you to check out our Encore Pro 540. Feel free to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815 if you have other questions!"}, {"answer_text": "Unfortunately there's no possible way. You'll need a different model, like something at the link below. 1-800-683-5715  https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07HM7GNB9?ref myi title dp"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx38PPVPU8KGPUK", "question_text": "What else do i need to make this compatible with the toshiba dp5032-sd digital telephone?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "The Toshiba DP5032-SD has a built in headset port.  So, all you will need is an A10 Modular Cable and you are all set."}, {"answer_text": "Hello! The HW251N headset will work correctly with your Toshiba phone, please note that the M22 amplifier will be required to connect."}, {"answer_text": "Hello, according to Plantronics compatibility guide you will need the M22 amplifier. If you have any further question please feel free to contact us at 1800-683-5715!  https://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-Vista-Amplifier-Certified-Refurbished/dp/B071KHKXRS/ref sr 1 3?s sporting-goods&ie UTF8&qid 1533150140&sr 8-3&keywords Plantronics+M22"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3GJN2TUB4AE3U", "question_text": "I use AT&T 1070 phones in the office. Do I need an adapter or can this go directly into the headset port?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "I believe you will need an adapter."}, {"answer_text": "Hi Dr. Bernstein, you'll need either the m22 amplifier or a qd to 2.5mm adapter to go with this plantronics headset and your AT&T 1070 phone. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions.  https://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-Cable-2-5MM-CA10SPARE-Increments/dp/B000086TIL/ref sr 1 1?ie UTF8&qid 1500261859&sr 8-1&keywords plantronics+qd+to+2.5mm https://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-Vista-Amplifier-Certified-Refurbished/dp/B071KHKXRS/ref sr 1 1?ie UTF8&qid 1500261885&sr 8-1&keywords plantronics+m22+certified%5C"}, {"answer_text": "this attaches to a plantronic headset base wont connect directly to phone"}, {"answer_text": "Please call Plantronics support line."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1ROTBEWTGSXZU", "question_text": "Is it compatible with avaya 9508", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi Jennifer, yes this headset is compatible but you will need to purchase the HIC adapter to go with the headset. Below is a link for you. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions. https://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-Adapter-Cable-Avaya-phones/dp/B00NNPQHAQ/ref sr 1 3?ie UTF8&qid 1466011028&sr 8-3&keywords 49323-46"}, {"answer_text": "yes, but you will need the Plantronics HIC adapter"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1BY75UZRD6O0P", "question_text": "What adapter do I need to connect this to a panasonic link to cell handset?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "i do not  know we purchase for use with landlines sorry"}, {"answer_text": "This is probably not the best handset for you.  You need a headset that has stereo connection.  There might be a Plantronics quick disconnect to stereo adapter but I am not aware of it.  Thank you."}, {"answer_text": "plantronic m22 or m12"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx76QIX1LANF1H", "question_text": "what adapter do I need for an  lg cell phone", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "wont work with cell phone"}, {"answer_text": "I don't know,  this headset was for a hard phone at work"}]}
{"question_id": "TxLY1KLB1I1TYT", "question_text": "Is this compatible with the cisco ip 7941 phone?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "This headset is compatible with the Cisco 7941 phone with the additional QD Modular plug cord."}, {"answer_text": "Hi there, you need the U10 direct connect cable. Part number 26715-01. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions"}]}
{"question_id": "TxHJVSWT64I0IZ", "question_text": "I have one sided hearing/hearing aid. The way it is oriented in the picture will not work with my hearing aid. Can it also go over the left ear?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes.  The microphone piece can be turned, to the device can be worn on either ear."}, {"answer_text": "I am not sure and I don't have it with now.   I can check it out on Monday, and then let you know."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx18UH9QZEG2C38", "question_text": "If I have this connected to the phone or not, can I hear a ringtone from the headset and not the phone.?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Unfortunately not. You'll need a wireless headset like at the link below if you want that feature. 1-800-683-5715  https://www.amazon.com/dp/B073V99416"}, {"answer_text": "Hello, the HW251N headset will only act as a speaker and microphone for your deskphone. In this case, the ringtone notification will come from the phone itself, this is because of the way the phone's headset port works. If you have any other questions, please don't hesitate to contact Plantronics Customer Care at 800-985-9815."}, {"answer_text": "No, you cannot hear the ring from the headset for incoming calls. It only comes from the phone"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx160B7I7EJC7FS", "question_text": "What adaptor do i need to use this headset with a panasonic kx-tga6860 cordless phone?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "cant do it"}, {"answer_text": "This is not the headset for you.  You need a headset with a stereo adapter."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1BKQ9W94AO3GS", "question_text": "I have an nec dt-400. what adapter do i need?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Most NEC DT series phones have a  headset \" port and can use the A10 Direct Connect QD cord.  If you want outbound voice volume control, a M22 Amplifier is used.\""}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2PE3PJTQIYR6P", "question_text": "I have a 67tb caption call phone, will this work with that and do i need some sort of adapter?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hello! Unfortunately we are unable to guarantee compatibility as your desk phone is not listed within our compatibility guide, nor we're able to recommend an accessory. If you have any other questions, please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at: 800-985-9815"}]}
{"question_id": "TxRZL3QPE4H0IY", "question_text": "Not clear on the need for an adapter. I want to use for dictation connecting to my pc's usb port. do i need an adapter or any extras?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hello, yes you will need to purchase a separate adapter in order to connect to your computer, which i will leave in the link below. Another great headset I recommend that does not require an adapter is the Discover D711u. Check it out below or please feel free to give us a call at 1800-683-5715 for any further questions you may have. :)  https://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-DA80-USB-Audio-Processor/dp/B00W2N5D1Y/ref sr 1 3?ie UTF8&qid 1516289392&sr 8-3&keywords DA70  https://www.amazon.com/Discover-D711U-Monaural-Softphone-Warranty/dp/B076TG2QF3/ref sr 1 1?s electronics&ie UTF8&qid 1516289432&sr 1-1&keywords D711u"}, {"answer_text": "You will need an adaptor to use it with a pc. It\u2019s an oddly shaped slot that won\u2019t fit in any plug for a Mac/pc I\u2019ve ever seen"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3UL7JY9CJX8FF", "question_text": "if I add a Plantronics 3.5 right angle QD cable will this head set connect directly to our IPhone 5 phones?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "yes, with the Plantronics 3.5 QD cable, yes"}, {"answer_text": "Hi James, a link below will be the adapter you need.   http://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-38541-02-MO300-Headphone-Cable/dp/B002GO25VU"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx21SWCPSI5NWSN", "question_text": "What connection is needed to use with Avaya phones?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi R, if you give me the model of Avaya phone you have I can help you better."}]}
{"question_id": "TxPQ0V34APM6HU", "question_text": "What type of plug-in end does this headset come with? Is it a regular phone cord end?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "It has what we call in the industry qd cord at the end. Basically you need to purchase another cord/amp so you can use this headset with your telephone. What phone are you trying to connect the headset to?"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3SIOOPTQ2TUX", "question_text": "what adapter/accessories needed for new Mitel phones?  is it the same for ShoreTel230?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Sorry guy! I don't know!"}, {"answer_text": "Hi! The typical adapter for a ShoreTel phone IP230 would be the A10-16 (66268-02) cable. The A10-16 is compatible with some Mitel phones, but we recommend you to access our Compatibility guide on our website so you can confirm the adapter required for your Mitel phone. Our Customer Care Team is available at: 800-985-9815 if you would like further assistance!"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2H425QYH7DCE", "question_text": "does it work on Avaya 9608G", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes, but it doesn not plug in directly to the headset jack on your phone, so you need the Plantronics HIS cable, Part Number: 72442-41. I do not have this part on Amazon but I'm sure you can find it. I can order a new one for you for $45 but I'm sure you can find a used one on Amazon. Thank you, Matt"}, {"answer_text": "YES ,, I have attached a link to anothers site with a good cross reference list. Scroll down and it will show the Plantronics HW251N is designed to work with the Avaya 9608G. http://headsetplus.com/category99 101/ Place your order today"}, {"answer_text": "Have no idea. Call plantronics directly"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx27RXP06RDN3QG", "question_text": "is this product neor refurbished?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx16FI0EGYLKV4E", "question_text": "What cord do i need to purchase to use the headset with a comtel phone? (rj9 headset port)", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "I purchased a quick disconnect cord that connect to the phone and then headset.  Works like a charm."}, {"answer_text": "Hi Joan, you will need to purchase an M12 or an M22 amplifier. Let us know if we can help further, 1-800-683-5715"}, {"answer_text": "The headset and the base set all fit into the phone through a regular phone jack. The S-10 comes with two pieces, the headset and the base set with an electrical connection and a phone connection. I have no idea why you would need a rj9 headset. Hope that helps"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3S9MNR80SCY7J", "question_text": "Will this work with the panasonic KX-DT343?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "DON'T KNOW, HAVE A NEC PHONE SYSTEM"}, {"answer_text": "I have no idea, I bought it for a friend."}, {"answer_text": "I'm not sure.  I bought it to work with my laptop."}, {"answer_text": "Sorry I don't know if it will work with you device.  I bought them for Cisco IP phones."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx10WSYUT7QHZXN", "question_text": "I would like to use this headset with a cisco CP-6921 phone. which adapter do i need?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi there, you need the 26716-01 cable or an m22 amplifier. Give us a call with any further questions at 1-800-683-5715."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2071NVELGTJIZ", "question_text": "Will this work with the Cisco CP-8811 model & i would need to buy the adapter also, correct?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes, it works but you need the Quick Disconnect cord, Part Number: 26716-01"}, {"answer_text": "yes it will and i will put quick disconnect cord with it"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3IOEB7TN3M93N", "question_text": "I'd like to get this for our office, we need a good wired headset for the polycom vvx501 phones.  will this plug in directly?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hello! According to our Compatibility Guide you will need to use the Vista M22 amplifier or the DA80 adapter in order to connect the headset into your desk phone. You will need to use one of these options since the connector of the headset itself is a Quick Disconnect. Please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance."}, {"answer_text": "Yes"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2LO588XI6VHNU", "question_text": "I have a toshiba phone model dp5022-sdm.  what cord do i need to buy to connect it to this phone?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi Kerry, you will need the M22 amplifier. Below is a link for you. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions. https://www.amazon.com/gp/offer-listing/B000NX3OMA/ref sr 1 2 olp?ie UTF8&qid 1472241171&sr 8-2&keywords m22&condition used"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2E3PVZMWR8SY1", "question_text": "Do I need some sort of adapter to use this with a Cisco IP 7945 phone?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi Carter, yes you will need the U10 adapter, part number 26716-01. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions."}, {"answer_text": "I plugged them into both my computer and my cell phone without using an adapter."}, {"answer_text": "I don't think so.  I am not absolutely sure.  The directions are included.  Amazon also has an exceptional return policy."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2NQDHLLXXF9LR", "question_text": "What adapter will I need to use with my Samsung S4 cell?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "GO TO www.plantronics.com and you will find answers to your questions."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2RGO7P2CS4YFQ", "question_text": "do I need an adapter for a Avaya model #700504844?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No"}, {"answer_text": "Hello! If you are referring to the Avaya 9608 model, you will need to use the HIS (P/N: 72442-41) quick disconnect cable in order to connect the headset into your desk phone. You can purchase this cable directly through one of our authorized distributors or resellers. Please don't hesitate to contact our Customer Care Team at 800-985-9815 if you require assistance or have further questions."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2YSFF9RK7BVTS", "question_text": "Does this headset work with broadview networks office suite phones?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "It works with all systems but usually you need the M22 amp."}, {"answer_text": "Hi Donna, yes but you will need an additional adapter depending on the model of broadview phone you have. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx18BBF9JKWEF1G", "question_text": "Will this fit into my Panasonic cordless phone?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi Janice, you would need to get the 2.5mm to QD headset adapter to go with this headset, then it would work with your cordless phone. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx22U1085W0TR11", "question_text": "Does this headset work with IPhone 5,6, 6+ with or without an adapter?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No, you need to buy an adapter to go from the plantronics headset to an iphone or other phone.  The end of the cable is the standard Plantronics quick disconnect.  With the adapter cable it works perfectly!  Use it all the time in my office when I disconnect from my Avaya phone and want to walk around talking on my iPhone.  Fantastic headset well worth the money!"}, {"answer_text": "Hi Jen, this headset will not work without the separate adapter purchased. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions."}, {"answer_text": "You will need a an additional adapter.  I"}, {"answer_text": "Definitely not"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1R2N1XXYL67DI", "question_text": "Does the headset come with the base and cord?", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi Tina, this headset comes with the headset only. You'll need the headset amplifier or direct connect cable, depending on your telephone. Give us a call at 1-800-683-5715 for any further questions."}, {"answer_text": "no just headset"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx38URSRPWMKEYX", "question_text": "Will this work with a lg 5012d phone, assuming i have the 27190-01 cable", "asin": "B000LSZ2D6", "bullet_point1": "Noise-Canceling microphone filters out background sound", "bullet_point2": "HW251N P/N 75100-06", "bullet_point3": "Uses Plantronics QD Quick Disconnect Connector. Must be used with Plantronics Amp or with proper phone or USB adapter cable", "bullet_point4": "Connectivity Technology: Wired, Earpiece Design: Over-the-head, Earpiece Type: Monaural, Host Interface: Proprietary, Microphone Design: Boom, Microphone Technology: Noise Canceling, Product Model: HW251N, Product Series: SupraPlus, Standard Warranty: 2 Year", "bullet_point5": "Easy Lightweight Wear -Leaving One Ear Uncovered For Person-to-Person Conversations", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Plantronics", "item_name": "Plantronics HW251N SupraPlus Wideband Headset (64338-31)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "You will require a QD to headphone cable/adapter."}, {"answer_text": "Hi Steve, you would need the QD-3.5mm adapter. Below is a link for you. https://www.amazon.com/Plantronics-Cable-Assy-Right-Angle/dp/B000COKYXM/ref sr 1 1?ie UTF8&qid 1474470966&sr 8-1&keywords plantronics+qd+to+3.5mm"}]}
{"question_id": "TxZMCTWFCINB3D", "question_text": "Is this the complete headset? As in top-cap, crown races, bearings, etc.", "asin": "B001C5HQN6", "bullet_point1": "1 1/8 Threadless", "bullet_point2": "Black", "bullet_point3": "Campagnolo compatible.", "bullet_point4": "", "bullet_point5": "", "product_description": "FSA Orbit CE Integrated Headset. 1 1/8 Threadless ,Black. Campagnolo compatible.45\u00b0, 42mm OD.", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "FSA Orbit CE Integrated Headset 1 1/8 Threadless Black. Campagnolo compatible", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "i ordered it, but i never got it. the only thing im not to sure that it comes with is the top cap. it should come with everything else"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx17OJ0IX8VKOQ1", "question_text": "does it work on xbxo one", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No they only work on the 360 xbox . I have both and use both.."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx21T944J4VVZC8", "question_text": "can i listen to music on my ipod and chat with friends on xbox at the same time if i use a headphone jack splitter?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "You would need some kind of mixer to get it to work. Two audio signals going to one set of speakers will only play whichever is more powerful. You would also need to make sure the splitter will carry the microphone signal. Most splitters only account for stereo output, not for microphone input. If you set it up so the Xbox is only using the the microphone it could work. So the input would use you iPod to play music while the mic is going to the Xbox. The Slyr uses a USB for the mic input and an RCA red and white for stereo input. So you could plug the iPod into the RCAs with an adaptor and the USB into the Xbox. You would have to test it to verify though."}, {"answer_text": "no, this product is terrible DO NOT BUY"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2PQN18ORRW2DP", "question_text": "Can I use the mix amp that it comes with on my Xbox One?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "I'm not sure but I used it with my PS4. I just did the 3.5 mm plug on my friend's Xbox One."}, {"answer_text": "Yes, it actually works very well, but there are ALOT of cords, at least 3-4 feet of the stuff, with another 4-5 ends. It gets tangled really easily, but besides that, the mix amp should work fine!"}, {"answer_text": "No only 360 and pc"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1OUK5OKFM50U3", "question_text": "No one can hear me on xbox one", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "it says on the box that the xbox one requires additional chat adapter ether then that I have no clue since I don't have a xbox one yet"}, {"answer_text": "You have to have the xbox one chat adapter"}]}
{"question_id": "TxZSJN77OR67G2", "question_text": "Does this have a usb connector?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "yeah"}, {"answer_text": "Yes, it has a USB jack for power. But, know that these headphones are very cheaply made with very weak plastic, and they're extremely uncomfortable. They're made to look cool and that's all they have to offer. Get the Turtle Beach X12 instead. Twice the quality, half the price."}, {"answer_text": "Yes it does"}, {"answer_text": "Yes it does. I have the rca's red & white connected to my ps3 so I can hear game sound, the usb is connected to my computer so I skype with my friends."}]}
{"question_id": "TxLVX2HPMI6BPN", "question_text": "Dos it work for Xbox 360?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "It should work"}, {"answer_text": "yes it does, has the wire/plug for it as well."}, {"answer_text": "Yes it does, has a dedicated port for it too"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3ES43LM8Z85WS", "question_text": "I own a Vizio TV that only has a green audio out (no red/white slots) and I use an HDMI with my Xbox 360. Will this headset work with my setup?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "You wouldn't be able to use the mixer that comes with the headset and the only way I can think of to use the headset is with an adapter. There's a tutorial on YouTube from Skullcandy that shows how to set up on the 360."}, {"answer_text": "Yes it should work in a couple different ways. The green connector will work, but i believe you can also use the USB uplink on the xbox or the tv."}, {"answer_text": "Unfortunately, I'm pretty sure that unless you have a red and a white jack, the mic and the headphones won't work. Sorry."}]}
{"question_id": "TxHFRIHGCT1LO4", "question_text": "Do they hook up to the game consoles like a pair of turtle beaches would essentially?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes. The cable has 2 different hookups on the end, One end plugs into the audio out and the other is the USB power.  Just like turtle beaches"}, {"answer_text": "Yes they do"}, {"answer_text": "they hook up via a usb cable. there are audio cords that plug into the tv"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1D48P4GKLRJ3Z", "question_text": "Does this work for xbox one S?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "It should work."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1QJXB9CYJWT41", "question_text": "dos the packige come with every thing to hook up to a xbox 360 ?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "It comes with the USB connector and you can just plug that into the Xbox but you only need the cord (the one smaller than the 3.5mm jack) if your Xbox requires that"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx4RB827GG4075", "question_text": "So, these are totally comparable with the Xbox One?. Any adapters needed?.", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Per Skullcandy....yes it works directly with xbox.  Al"}, {"answer_text": "You only need an adapter if you don't have the latest controller. The microphone does work when plugged into the Microsoft adapter."}, {"answer_text": "Per Skullcandy....yes it works directly with xbox.  Al"}, {"answer_text": "I use mine with PS4.  I would guess that they would also be compatible with Xbox 1, it came with a ton of different connectors."}, {"answer_text": "If you bought a newer Xbox one controller you should have no problem but if you have not bought an after market you will need an Xbox sterio adapter"}, {"answer_text": "WARNING: the  in-line mixer \" is only compatible with PC and last-gen consoles! If you wish to use this with the Xbox One, you'll need that Xbox one headphone controller adapter. No idea if the mic will work when plugged in that way.\""}]}
{"question_id": "Tx14C05GKV813VJ", "question_text": "how good are these for fps gaming?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Great...excellent sound and nice mic that you can tuck away."}, {"answer_text": "They're really solid for fps games. One of the three settings (I forgot which one it was) allows you to boost the sound of enemy footsteps. It helps a lot, especially in cod or battlefield :)"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1YRTIKP88NYKC", "question_text": "What adapter do I need for Xbox one", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Look up xbox one chat adapter"}, {"answer_text": "The xbox one stereo headset. Or if you have a controller with a 3.5 mm jack just the aux cable."}, {"answer_text": "I am not sure what it is called but I was told you could find them at Game Stop"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3W4TQDVYQ6JC9", "question_text": "let me get this straight. cause im not 100% sure. i can plug in the included shorter cable for a phone? the hesh 2's are too bulky for school", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "yup"}, {"answer_text": "Yea you can plug in the shorter cable into a phone."}, {"answer_text": "Yes, there is a cable that plugs into the headset, then plugs into the device that plugs into your pc/console. Or it can be plugged into a phone or mp3 player, etc. Its long but not too long, about the same length as most earbuds."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3587B03RAOQVZ", "question_text": "can you plug it in to a ps4 controller", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes"}, {"answer_text": "its not possible to plug this headset into the controller however u can plug it directly into the system"}, {"answer_text": "yes you can."}, {"answer_text": "Yes"}, {"answer_text": "NO"}, {"answer_text": "Yes"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx173AKTJHR6LBS", "question_text": "Can i use it on a ps4 without an adaptor?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "i am not sure of the inputs on the ps4 but it has a usb port connector and the 3.5mm jack connector also so if the ps4 is able to use any of those connections, then you can use it"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx167F8BMGXS5FR", "question_text": "does it do both chat and game audio on the xbox one when using the adapter", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "I don't have an XBox but on my PS3, I put it all the was to game then i give it one click to the voice side. For added volume on the PS3, you can adjust voice volume under accessory."}, {"answer_text": "Yea"}, {"answer_text": "Yes but your going to be experiencing issues while trying to adjust BOTH the adaptor volume and the Skull candy volume."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2J5IX2H5NBGDO", "question_text": "Will it work with a Mac for Skype calls?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Absolutely, i own a mac and i use them all the time, also i can use them to take phone calls when im lazy. The mic is very good."}, {"answer_text": "Yes"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx23GSCRCADPN28", "question_text": "this product works with Xbox ONE???????", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Kinda, you need to buy the adaptor from Microsoft. Then buy a cable for the audio input, which is around $5. But you'll experience issues such as adjusting the mic and volume. I personally won't recommend this for the xbox one. Just get the Skullcandy SLYR for xbox one.."}]}
{"question_id": "TxO5ACSM46JPZF", "question_text": "do I need an adapter to use these with xbox 360?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No"}, {"answer_text": "No"}, {"answer_text": "No"}, {"answer_text": "No"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx12QOFTLROE3X0", "question_text": "Do they work with xbox one?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No they don't , but let's hope that Microsoft makes a wireless headset"}, {"answer_text": "Yes.   Here's my husband's response :   3 1/2 stars because you have to buy an adapter to be able to talk through the headset. I've never purchased the adapter because I can't find a place that actually sells it. \"\""}, {"answer_text": "Yes."}, {"answer_text": "Yes they should. The Skullcandy SLYR is USB powered, and the Xbox One has 3 USB ports."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2QABMEP18DT29", "question_text": "can you listen to music and have game audio going though the headset at the same time ?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes. Any headset will do that."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx44B5XIMFBFEU", "question_text": "Do I need the Xbox one adapter to use the headset for the Xbox one?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes you will need the adaptor for use with the Xbox one.  However, I  have heard that there is a SLYR  headset coming out that is   just   for the Xbox One. I  think the price will be ninety some dollars and be sporting the Halo game look in a white coat.  So now you can buy this awesome headset and buy a 25  dollar adaptor or buy the entire thing together with a halo look,  listeners preference.  :-)"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3SQYG3EN37Q1F", "question_text": "Does it have mic monitoring, or the ability to hear yourself speak through the headset so you are not shouting?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No"}, {"answer_text": "Yes"}, {"answer_text": "Yes"}, {"answer_text": "Not really sure.  I know when testing the mic in the OS settings I can hear myself clearly.  During game play I could only hear those who I was talking with.  When checking with them they stated that I was a mid volume but fully understandable.  I think the mic sits far enough away from the mouth as to not cause  Shouting \".\""}, {"answer_text": "No"}, {"answer_text": "No"}, {"answer_text": "No"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3LNODO82XU03E", "question_text": "Does this connect to PS4", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "I am not sure. I would call Game Stop and ask them or ur local video store."}, {"answer_text": "Yez it does"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1K0PNUWTQZZ40", "question_text": "Can these be used for wii u?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Good Morning!  Per Skullcandy, they should work.  Thanks!   Al"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx475WXGYVPLHZ", "question_text": "what is the difference between these and the xb1 edition?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "The only difference is sound quality, and quality of the mic"}, {"answer_text": "This edition of the Skullcandy SLYR's is compatible with only PC PS3 and Xbox 360 where as the Xbox One edition is only compatible with the Xbox one. The Skullcandy website can answer a lot of questions about platform conflicts."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1JAPC4X0LNMPE", "question_text": "Are these cups large enough for big ears over long periods of time gaming?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "They are very good for long periods of time because i play cs:Go for 3-4 hours straight and no pain or anything, very comfortable. Hope this helps."}, {"answer_text": "They are pretty comfortable for 2-3 hours. The ear piece has foam like covering which makes it easier on your ears."}, {"answer_text": "Depends on ear size I would say I have larger than normal ears for a few hours a night they are fine to wear, they tend to make you sweat a little, other than that they are fine, more preferable I would get wireless instead"}, {"answer_text": "No"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2QD4JTDO7NR50", "question_text": "Are they wireless", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No, they have a really long cord."}, {"answer_text": "Hello C.J. - No they are not.  However they cable supplied is a lot longer than most.  Also, they disconnect at the headphones as well as the volume control, so they will just pop out if you accidentally step on them most likely.  I am using them right now, so they are the longest lasting headset I have ever had."}, {"answer_text": "No not at all but still awesome"}, {"answer_text": "No. They have amazing sound quality. But there's wires. It you want to keep playing with an HDMI you need to get the PLYR edition headset."}, {"answer_text": "No not at all but still awesome"}, {"answer_text": "There is a wireless variant, but these are wired. Though I have no experience with the wireless product, I can say that with multiple inputs and a long cord, my own SLYR can get awfully tangled."}]}
{"question_id": "TxKLSCK73ZEACL", "question_text": "how is it used with xbox 360 ?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Plug it in"}, {"answer_text": "It has the connection similar to turtle beaches. 2.5mm plug or so."}, {"answer_text": "It plugs into the TV using the Red,White,Yellow cables. The cables have a slot on-top of them so you plug in the xbox cables. Then it works as a headset for xbox, same goes for the PS3."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3OAJBB3LWUUZ0", "question_text": "Are these compatible with Windows 8.1?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes its compatible with windows 8.1 and windows 10."}, {"answer_text": "Yup, running 8.1 with mine, it probably works fine with win10 too, there isnt a huge difference."}, {"answer_text": "Yes but it only has one 4 pin 3.5mm jack so you need a headphone splitter if you want to use it on pc"}, {"answer_text": "I've tried to use them on my computer but I wasn't successful. It's most likely are but I doubt know the greatest amount about computers."}, {"answer_text": "They work on Windows 10 and 8 so yes they should work on Windows 8.1."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx21RR5LBYXX9MK", "question_text": "How do these compare to Uproars in terms of sound quality?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "The sound quality is really really good, but after a few years it slowly declines, but overall stays pretty loud. I once had someone mistake the sound quality for a $200 dollar pair of beats..."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx92TS1W6HG84H", "question_text": "what about the sounds for xplosions an that kind of sounds?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "The sound quality for sound effects like explosions is exceptional.  The quality of the low range of sounds is excellent so it really picks up rich sound effects."}, {"answer_text": "I play fps games with it and the explosions are really good. I'm not an audio expert though so"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx8AGU5AGKU149", "question_text": "is it good for listening music?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "It is great for listening to music. It has a bass booster and bass control. Hope this will help."}, {"answer_text": "They are very good to hear music"}, {"answer_text": "Absolutely. The sound quality is excellent."}, {"answer_text": "Yes they are pretty good not a lot of bass so I would download a tuning app on your phone or iPod either than that they don't slip and Are comfortable"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx39F9KD9G3BJCU", "question_text": "Does this work with PC? If it does how?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes it does work on pc.   I personally just plug it into the headphone jack on my pc. If you want to use the extension cord that it come with it, you'll have to plug it into a usb port, then plug the headphones in. The headphones also come with a detailed instruction manual that shows you how to hook it up. I love my slyr headphones, and would recommend it to everyone."}, {"answer_text": "Yes it does, but i  bouth them for my ps4 not my Pc"}, {"answer_text": "Yes you can use it with PC  use it with The USB cable  Windows will found it  )"}, {"answer_text": "Yes it does! It just plugs into the conputer. It has a ton of different plugs to use in different things. My boys like them as they are very comfy"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1D4TQALBJCSQB", "question_text": "How is the sound quality on a mobile phone? Do you get the same sorround sound?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "It's not exactly the same because not all phones support surround sound but the quality of the sound itself is still top notch and the and it still gets pretty loud"}, {"answer_text": "Sorry. I don't know. I don't think you can use the mobile phone on this"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx5KYW3J2II8RE", "question_text": "Does the in-line mixer work on PC? (Seperate chat & game audio)", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes - it should work on Mac and PC."}, {"answer_text": "the headphones plug in via USB"}, {"answer_text": "Got this headset for my 12 year old and he says that the headset has a USB plug that has the mixer attached to it, so you can use is on PC. But if you PC does not have a USB plug, the Mic will not work, hope this helps Cheers."}, {"answer_text": "No. But the headset its self has a removable 3.5 mm auxiliary jack where you can replace the original cable. If your using a PC that has 3.5 mm mic jack and a headphone jack you'll need 3.5 mm female to 3.5 mm male splitter which is usually 2 to 3 dollars. But if your pic has one auxiliary jack like mobile devices which is both mic and headphone jack rather way the headset its self works perfectly for pc but no the mixer does not work on it. Hope this helped!!!"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx205RBBSFT2L6D", "question_text": "What do i need to hook it up to a ps4?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Per Skullcandy, it will work directly with PS4   Thanks!"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx20A14MKMX5DZY", "question_text": "I can use these fully wireless right?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No. They are definitely corded. One cool feature: they disconnect from the earpiece as well as the other end.  If you have any problems, check to make sure that they are connected well on both ends."}, {"answer_text": "No they have a 3.5 jack"}]}
{"question_id": "TxR2INQYUBABBB", "question_text": "will it work on the ps3?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes, that's the only reason I own them!"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1DM9O26RECNI5", "question_text": "Can you use it on playstation 4", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "As long as you have something that has audio components like I have, yes. I have an hdmi to component converter in order to use mine on my tv. I have an old tv. Without this, I doubt it would work. But I am not 100% sure. But doing it the way I did allowed me to use it on my ps4."}, {"answer_text": "Yes. I use it on a ps4, I highly reccomend it!"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3AEJWB5SR5UBQ", "question_text": "does it connect wirelessly to android and ios devices?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No"}, {"answer_text": "Look I don't know why the other guy says yes this this is Awsome it's the most comfortable headset out there and I have a pair of turtle beach earforce tangos but this headset is wired if you would like to hook it up wirelessly you need to buy a 20 device called an indigo bluetooth transmitter/reciever. Or just buy the refurbished earforce tangos there 99 dollars right now and I own both a new and refurbished pair and both work great"}, {"answer_text": "No"}, {"answer_text": "Yes"}, {"answer_text": "No"}, {"answer_text": "No"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2UT3QG8UPHVV2", "question_text": "are these compatible with the ps3?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes."}, {"answer_text": "Yes it works fine :)"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx130PLQONHHONM", "question_text": "works with ps4? how is it with call of duty and does it drain your battery on your controller?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Gotta connect slyr to ps4 directly to use it because of the mixer and no headphone cord make it work its better for the pc."}, {"answer_text": "My brother is the gamer and I had him answer your question. He said it works great with all his systems including ps4. He loves it with COD and he said it doesn't drain the battery."}, {"answer_text": "Its like using any other ps4 headset except it will allow you to hear game audio also, no it doesn't drain your battery as far as I know."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2M1ZYP18QAE1S", "question_text": "Does it work with the PS4?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes any console you just have to buy adapters  like the turtle beach Dolby dss by ear force or mic adapters I had to buy those for my xbox one"}]}
{"question_id": "TxORBIRHZB26IY", "question_text": "does this come with any sort of case? or bag?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "It just come in a box. No storage bags."}, {"answer_text": "no case nor bag"}, {"answer_text": "Nope."}]}
{"question_id": "TxQY405NZ3EP4T", "question_text": "It works with play station 4?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes. It should work with PS4. :D"}, {"answer_text": "Depends on what you mean by work with the PS4. The mixer cable/box probably won't work but I plug it in directly to the PS4 controller using the supplied 3.5mm TRRS cable and it works just fine."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1VJIHGGF1GDIN", "question_text": "Is this compatible with Xbox one?", "asin": "B009RXUNGM", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Black/Yellow (SMSLFY-207)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "The Skullcandy SLYR is compatible with the XBox One. It has adapters specifically for it, in fact."}]}
{"question_id": "TxEUZM9JHEIS6J", "question_text": "Will it work with a polycom vvx 250?", "asin": "B011O2J5A8", "bullet_point1": "PC Stereo Headset Adapter Converts Dual 3.5mm to RJ Plug", "bullet_point2": "Still get great quality stereo sound from headset via this adapter", "bullet_point3": "All functions on headset and phone would function same", "bullet_point4": "Easy Setup, Plug and Play", "bullet_point5": "Only Work with Some Specific Phones in Description. Only buy it if you have one of the phone models listed in description below.", "product_description": "With this adapter, user can easily use exist PC computer stereo headset dual 3.5mm plug to work with IP phone Jack (please see compatible models below). One end is RJ Plug that will fit in the IP phone headset port, the other end are two dual adapter for the pc stereo headset plugs. COMPATIBLE PHONE LIST: BUY ONLY IF YOU HAVE ONE OF THE PHONE MODELS IN LIST   Nortel:i2002 (NTDU91), i2004 (NTDU92), i2007 (NTDU96)  Cisco:E20 video phone  PolycomIP Phones:IP 300, 301, 335, 430, 450, 500, 501, 550, 560, 600, 601, 650, 670, CX200, CX300, CX500, CX600, CX700, VVX300, VVX310, VVX 400, VVX410, VVX500, VVX600, VVX1500  Digium Phones:Digium D40, Digium D45, Digium D50,Digium D70  Altigen:AT-500, AT-510, IP-600, IP-705, IP-710, IP-720 Phones  Comdial:8312 8412  Shoretel:420, 480, 480G, 485  Starleaf:2210  Aastra models:6731i, 6735i, 6737i, 7446i, 9112i, 9133i, 9116, 9143i and 9480i", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Audicom Pc Headset Adapter Computer Stereo Headphone Dual 3.5mm to Rj9/Rj10 Phone Jack Converter for Aastra Shoretel Cisco E20 Polycom 335 VVX400 Digium D40 D70 Altigen Telephone IP Phones(PC35-STAC)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes,it will  work with a polycom vvx 250."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3IZVLH89LYT85", "question_text": "will this work with iphone headphones?", "asin": "B011O2J5A8", "bullet_point1": "PC Stereo Headset Adapter Converts Dual 3.5mm to RJ Plug", "bullet_point2": "Still get great quality stereo sound from headset via this adapter", "bullet_point3": "All functions on headset and phone would function same", "bullet_point4": "Easy Setup, Plug and Play", "bullet_point5": "Only Work with Some Specific Phones in Description. Only buy it if you have one of the phone models listed in description below.", "product_description": "With this adapter, user can easily use exist PC computer stereo headset dual 3.5mm plug to work with IP phone Jack (please see compatible models below). One end is RJ Plug that will fit in the IP phone headset port, the other end are two dual adapter for the pc stereo headset plugs. COMPATIBLE PHONE LIST: BUY ONLY IF YOU HAVE ONE OF THE PHONE MODELS IN LIST   Nortel:i2002 (NTDU91), i2004 (NTDU92), i2007 (NTDU96)  Cisco:E20 video phone  PolycomIP Phones:IP 300, 301, 335, 430, 450, 500, 501, 550, 560, 600, 601, 650, 670, CX200, CX300, CX500, CX600, CX700, VVX300, VVX310, VVX 400, VVX410, VVX500, VVX600, VVX1500  Digium Phones:Digium D40, Digium D45, Digium D50,Digium D70  Altigen:AT-500, AT-510, IP-600, IP-705, IP-710, IP-720 Phones  Comdial:8312 8412  Shoretel:420, 480, 480G, 485  Starleaf:2210  Aastra models:6731i, 6735i, 6737i, 7446i, 9112i, 9133i, 9116, 9143i and 9480i", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Audicom Pc Headset Adapter Computer Stereo Headphone Dual 3.5mm to Rj9/Rj10 Phone Jack Converter for Aastra Shoretel Cisco E20 Polycom 335 VVX400 Digium D40 D70 Altigen Telephone IP Phones(PC35-STAC)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No, this  doesn't work."}]}
{"question_id": "TxABHA63HN5VW0", "question_text": "Will this work with polycom vvx 400 and 410?", "asin": "B011O2J5A8", "bullet_point1": "PC Stereo Headset Adapter Converts Dual 3.5mm to RJ Plug", "bullet_point2": "Still get great quality stereo sound from headset via this adapter", "bullet_point3": "All functions on headset and phone would function same", "bullet_point4": "Easy Setup, Plug and Play", "bullet_point5": "Only Work with Some Specific Phones in Description. Only buy it if you have one of the phone models listed in description below.", "product_description": "With this adapter, user can easily use exist PC computer stereo headset dual 3.5mm plug to work with IP phone Jack (please see compatible models below). One end is RJ Plug that will fit in the IP phone headset port, the other end are two dual adapter for the pc stereo headset plugs. COMPATIBLE PHONE LIST: BUY ONLY IF YOU HAVE ONE OF THE PHONE MODELS IN LIST   Nortel:i2002 (NTDU91), i2004 (NTDU92), i2007 (NTDU96)  Cisco:E20 video phone  PolycomIP Phones:IP 300, 301, 335, 430, 450, 500, 501, 550, 560, 600, 601, 650, 670, CX200, CX300, CX500, CX600, CX700, VVX300, VVX310, VVX 400, VVX410, VVX500, VVX600, VVX1500  Digium Phones:Digium D40, Digium D45, Digium D50,Digium D70  Altigen:AT-500, AT-510, IP-600, IP-705, IP-710, IP-720 Phones  Comdial:8312 8412  Shoretel:420, 480, 480G, 485  Starleaf:2210  Aastra models:6731i, 6735i, 6737i, 7446i, 9112i, 9133i, 9116, 9143i and 9480i", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Audicom Pc Headset Adapter Computer Stereo Headphone Dual 3.5mm to Rj9/Rj10 Phone Jack Converter for Aastra Shoretel Cisco E20 Polycom 335 VVX400 Digium D40 D70 Altigen Telephone IP Phones(PC35-STAC)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes,it work with polycom vvx 400 and 410."}]}
{"question_id": "TxD57S0VXOBRZ9", "question_text": "which company earphones would be compatible for this?", "asin": "B011O2J5A8", "bullet_point1": "PC Stereo Headset Adapter Converts Dual 3.5mm to RJ Plug", "bullet_point2": "Still get great quality stereo sound from headset via this adapter", "bullet_point3": "All functions on headset and phone would function same", "bullet_point4": "Easy Setup, Plug and Play", "bullet_point5": "Only Work with Some Specific Phones in Description. Only buy it if you have one of the phone models listed in description below.", "product_description": "With this adapter, user can easily use exist PC computer stereo headset dual 3.5mm plug to work with IP phone Jack (please see compatible models below). One end is RJ Plug that will fit in the IP phone headset port, the other end are two dual adapter for the pc stereo headset plugs. COMPATIBLE PHONE LIST: BUY ONLY IF YOU HAVE ONE OF THE PHONE MODELS IN LIST   Nortel:i2002 (NTDU91), i2004 (NTDU92), i2007 (NTDU96)  Cisco:E20 video phone  PolycomIP Phones:IP 300, 301, 335, 430, 450, 500, 501, 550, 560, 600, 601, 650, 670, CX200, CX300, CX500, CX600, CX700, VVX300, VVX310, VVX 400, VVX410, VVX500, VVX600, VVX1500  Digium Phones:Digium D40, Digium D45, Digium D50,Digium D70  Altigen:AT-500, AT-510, IP-600, IP-705, IP-710, IP-720 Phones  Comdial:8312 8412  Shoretel:420, 480, 480G, 485  Starleaf:2210  Aastra models:6731i, 6735i, 6737i, 7446i, 9112i, 9133i, 9116, 9143i and 9480i", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Audicom Pc Headset Adapter Computer Stereo Headphone Dual 3.5mm to Rj9/Rj10 Phone Jack Converter for Aastra Shoretel Cisco E20 Polycom 335 VVX400 Digium D40 D70 Altigen Telephone IP Phones(PC35-STAC)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Depends on how you are going to use it. I used mine to connect RJ9 jack on plantronic wireless headset base to separate mic and speaker Jacks on computer. If you connect the RJ9 to a supported phone, any computer headset with separate mic and speaker plugs should work."}]}
{"question_id": "TxU3NWROBZ3Q25", "question_text": "Is this headset wireless with Xbox one because I can\u2019t figure it out", "asin": "B012H842J2", "bullet_point1": "", "bullet_point2": "", "bullet_point3": "", "bullet_point4": "", "bullet_point5": "", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Wireless Stereo Pro Gaming Headset Headphone with mic for PS3/4 Xbox One 360 PC", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "You need to connect the optical cable from the transmitter to the xbox, and then connect the USB cable to the transmitter and then into your xbox. If using with the Kinect, you must connect the headset to your controller."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3IMU9HOCYJEV2", "question_text": "Does this headset require a separate purchase of an adapter for use with Xbox One?", "asin": "B012H842J2", "bullet_point1": "", "bullet_point2": "", "bullet_point3": "", "bullet_point4": "", "bullet_point5": "", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Wireless Stereo Pro Gaming Headset Headphone with mic for PS3/4 Xbox One 360 PC", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "This comes with everything you will need to use with xbox one."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2VFYO2WXQ8T20", "question_text": "Do these work with playstation 4", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Well you won't be able to use the mic/sound control, but you can still use the headset by plugging the 2.5mm jack into your PS4 controller"}]}
{"question_id": "TxPQEMZ09AN3AK", "question_text": "Is is compatable with an Hp laptop ? My sons port is for headphones. Im trying to find a headset that will allow him to use that and the mic", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes it indeed is. I've been switching between this headset and one from Razer. The cushioning is decent as well. Keep in mind, the cord is detachable for easy stowing."}, {"answer_text": "Yes it is compatible with the laptop and any other items with a jack available."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2UEIMPT8H9SJI", "question_text": "does it work for an xbox 1?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "As long as your controller has a 3.5 headset jack, which I know comes standard on the One S controllers, then yes it works with Xbox one."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx9JYS73KO3OOA", "question_text": "How do these headphones connect to the Xbox360 controller?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "They connect directly to the system and your television. I use PlayStation. Hope this helps!"}, {"answer_text": "Yes, you plug one part of a mic control into your Xbox and then plug the included 2.5mm cable into your controller."}, {"answer_text": "There should be a thinner wire that came with the headset that enables you to connect to your Xbox 360 controller."}, {"answer_text": "For your current headphones?"}, {"answer_text": "I have a ps4"}, {"answer_text": "It's hard to describe in words how the mic control works in words, I recommend watching a YouTube vid to see the part of the headset control where you plug in the headphones and 2.5mm cable. If you got this headset I believe you could use your monster headphones with the mic control or use the slyrs."}, {"answer_text": "I'm not sure but I think you need the audio control that comes with these headphones or something similar to that not just an adapter, but I'm not totally sure."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx33DCR8ORMTFQH", "question_text": "Is the headphone jack 3.5mm or 2.5mm? Will it work with the XBOX ONE headset adapter?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Low audio, bad quality"}, {"answer_text": "Not sure what size it was but it worked on the jack for my xbox controller."}, {"answer_text": "Hey there. It is a 3.5 mm jack. I am not sure about the adapter I recommend doing more research."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3Q42OXO8C677O", "question_text": "Okay, I want to get this for my gamer son, but what will I need to make sure it works with his Xbox One?  Does it need that headset adapter?  Thanks!!", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No"}, {"answer_text": "No don't think so, it comes with a whole bunch of different plugs that looks like it can plug into anything. My son thinks it does plug into the Xbox as is."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx33S0Y5T2EL8XR", "question_text": "Is this compatible with the Xbox One?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "I have a ps4 not a One so im not sure but i would think yes"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1AE275O4FD49Z", "question_text": "Will this work without the adaptor on the second gen Xbox one controllers?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No the adapter is required"}, {"answer_text": "Yes you can plug it in and use it, but you wont be able to mute the mic or adjust the volume. I would still highly recommend the adapter as it still fits in the second generation controller"}, {"answer_text": "Yes. Works with controllers that have a 3.5mm jack. Use the in game Xbox mixer in the settings to adjust balance, mute mic, and other settings."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1YCPNZGQNZ8SL", "question_text": "Does it work with ps4", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes this works with PS4"}]}
{"question_id": "TxSAGFY6LA6HYV", "question_text": "can i use on ps3", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes. They work on ps3 and Xbox 360. I think it also works on ps4."}, {"answer_text": "Yes some wieres wont be used."}, {"answer_text": "Yeah."}, {"answer_text": "Yes, you should be able to"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx277XLWA57UQ6R", "question_text": "does this work with a Mac? I need it for conference calls.", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "It plugs in using USB so it should work."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx7IVE8UVVHX1T", "question_text": "Will this worm", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "First off I need a proper question before I can give you an answer"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3R3A9KWKYICEW", "question_text": "Can this double as a headset for iPhone?  Will it work as speakers only no mic for iPhone?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "yes it will. I currently use this for my day job."}, {"answer_text": "Yes, in order for the mic to work you need to to plug it in via USB. If you only use the AUX cord and plug it into the headphones and your phone, it will only allow the speakers to work."}, {"answer_text": "It works as as a headset for any smartphone. Both the speakers and mic. By using the 3.5mm audio cable by itself. It doesn't have any controls for the device built in though."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1QT40C0RNYEOU", "question_text": "Will this headset's game and chat audio work with both next gen consoles? (Xbox One and PS4)", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes but you need purchase adapters to make the audio sound better and like with any console boy a sound processor to enhance audio, the processor makes my skullcandy slayers sound smooth and crisp as well as my turtle beach ear force tangos. I would recommend the Dolby dss sound processor from turtle beach"}, {"answer_text": "Hello David, Yes this headset works on PS4 And Xbox one Also the sound is Very Very Good.... Very good I headset I recommend it!!"}, {"answer_text": "Yes I believe so, my good friend has the xbox one and the skull candy slyr headset and he said they do and he loves them to"}, {"answer_text": "It barely works for currwnt gen or anything for that matter this is a no go"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1KXSMR8RUXY7Z", "question_text": "will this work with the new xbox one controllers?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes but you need to buy the Xbox one mic adapter for it"}, {"answer_text": "Yeah,but you need the mic adapter."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx20NKF9M6UYTUC", "question_text": "Is this a wired mic?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yea it's wired but it's a nice pair of headphones I'd definitely recommend it cuz u get ur money's worth."}, {"answer_text": "Yes, headset jack"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1D233LEZ7JYDJ", "question_text": "does this have a head phone jack or usb?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Both.  From the head set it connects via 3.5 to the controllet which connects via usb or rca."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1SUEZ7P45DH1X", "question_text": "I work in a call center and i\u2019m looking to use these wirelessly to take calls at work? anybody use them in a similar way? it\u2019d be nice because then i\u2019", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "They are a wired headset."}, {"answer_text": "They wouldn't work well. The cord had a piece specifically designed for an xbox controller. If you remove that and plug a normal AUX cord into the headset only the left side works (the side with the mic.) I've used them because I have to do voice recordings for a language class and I can honestly say the sound quality with a regular AUX cord is awful, so whoever you're speaking with may not be able to hear you clearly either."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1WXNT1H2ENK0J", "question_text": "can these headphones be used with a PS4?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yeah, you have to plug the headset to the controller. Just 1 wire that is about 6 feet long."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2RA6GWB1AEJ9X", "question_text": "Is this compatible with the Xbox One?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes, but I would just save up and go for turtle beach or some other brand... these aren\u2019t necessarily the greatest"}]}
{"question_id": "TxDLVUFRIFLR6U", "question_text": "Is this a wireless headset", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No it's not it does have a long wire for multiple connections"}, {"answer_text": "No, it is wired. But in my opinion, the wired are a better option because you can use them as headphones also. They sound amazing for music and gaming, and i highly recommend them!"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2RAO2749487ZI", "question_text": "Will this work with a newer virson Xbox One controller with the 3.5mm jack?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "If it's the same jack with iPhone , then it should be fine."}]}
{"question_id": "TxXCLIS90JNTDE", "question_text": "Is this headset compatible with the xbox one?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Jes, Jes it is."}, {"answer_text": "You'll have to buy the adapter which cost an extra $25"}]}
{"question_id": "TxPAV017UOGWLL", "question_text": "will this work for PC", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Absolutely. It has a USB jack on it, and if you are alright with stereo you can simply plug it into the headphones port. If you use the USB, the drivers may be a bit difficult, but that'll happen with any surround sound headset. The biggest problem I've encountered so far was solved simply by opening  Devices and Printers \" in the Start Menu.\""}, {"answer_text": "Yes, some PCs will even have an audio setting  specifically for skullcandy headsets"}, {"answer_text": "Yeah, pretty much any console."}, {"answer_text": "Yes, it's work on PC & console like PS3,PS4 & Xbox. The sound quality is really good."}]}
{"question_id": "TxB76QXIB01MSN", "question_text": "Are they wireless?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "no"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3E83BQ3QHVQNB", "question_text": "how long is the wire?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "The wire is pretty decent. It stretches all the way across my room and it's about 13 feet or so."}, {"answer_text": "Its about 2 ft but you can replace it with any size cable you want. I believe its a 3.5mm male connection on both sides."}, {"answer_text": "The cords are lengthy. The one from the controller to the headset is plenty long and the others that plug into the TV are almost too long"}, {"answer_text": "About 15 20 feet"}, {"answer_text": "It is pretty long. Around 6 to 8 feet"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx37Z3L194UU4IK", "question_text": "How long will these headphones be on sale?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Till black Friday"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx26D5ZXJL70HR2", "question_text": "Can I use this by connecting it directly into my ps4 controller", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes you can but you will experience feedback issues,  its not worth it. Just go with the usb set up, plugging it into the controller is more of an xbox thing."}, {"answer_text": "Yes you can, but you only will be able to hear audio chat."}, {"answer_text": "Yes, it will connect directly to a ps4 controller."}, {"answer_text": "Yes that's what I do"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2U9WIG3QFTUDQ", "question_text": "work with xbox one???", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "with the stereo headset adapter with is not included"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1GGPG3RHDZC6P", "question_text": "how long is the cable?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Around 6-7'"}, {"answer_text": "The wire is from the headset to the controller and it\u2019s about 1-2 feet long"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3VWWJW9KB9N63", "question_text": "will the headset itself play audio", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes I use it with my phone on trips"}, {"answer_text": "If you are asking if it is able to be plugged into a phone to listen to music with, the answer is yes."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2ERAQA7H32NGU", "question_text": "Does this work with the nintendo switch?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "If it has a 3.5mm output for the cable or a usb slot then it should be compatible"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1L3PSDL9S2KD0", "question_text": "Will this headset work with an Xbox One S controller ?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes, only if you have the Xbox Adapter or a new controller with a 3.5mm jack. So yes."}, {"answer_text": "Hello, Derek! Yes, I believe it does."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2HYXD1CQKJAE3", "question_text": "What size jack is the male end?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "i use it on my ps4 an most electronics i tablets pc cell phone  does come with an adaptor like for the size of an x box  if need be smaller  the maine connection is trough usb also so you can use it in various ways mine are still in good condition they are kind of big but  don t brake easy or anything"}, {"answer_text": "Read the description jackass"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx29VCVO53O8XDF", "question_text": "Will these work with PS4", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes they will"}, {"answer_text": "Yes.  Both with the 3.5 into the controller and via usb to the console."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx13OARNYYJ7S5I", "question_text": "Just want to confirm, both audio and voice are compatible on the PS4? I've seen conflicting info saying that it's only audio.", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Definitely is. I have had 2 pair of these bad boys since Christmas 2013. The audio is played from the TV Audio out port with a GMX Mixer powered by a USB cable. If you want you can completely remove the GMX Mixer from play and plug it directly into your PS4 Controller. I don't recommend it unless you are in party though because you lose a lot of audio that way."}, {"answer_text": "I have both this and a ps4, and all I can say is not compatible. It puts out sound, but your voice chat doesn't work"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1V1F8MWCHTPC7", "question_text": "Works with an iPhone?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes"}, {"answer_text": "Yes it works with any average phone jack. That is 3.5mm headphone jack"}, {"answer_text": "Yes it does"}, {"answer_text": "Yes... Ish. If you use the mic there's feedback. Also, the cord may not fit when your phone is in its case."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx32E1XAZ3Z47SB", "question_text": "Do I need a mic filter for breathing and the pops and stuff your mouth makes", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "no I don't use one and haven't had any trouble."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx13FXURTNR6FEN", "question_text": "do these only work with the old style xbox one controller?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "They will work on all Xbox one controllers."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2V9AINEAJWREG", "question_text": "Can these switch between listening to music in stereo and talking on the phone (mono/both ears) on an iPhone via bluetooth?", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "umm i dont know try looking at the specs some more"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx34RSFJKVLT42Q", "question_text": "do you recomend something else", "asin": "B009RXUOD4", "bullet_point1": "SUPREME SOUND - Proprietary Supreme Sound technology delivers powerful bass and precision highs", "bullet_point2": "EZ STASH MIC - Boom mic quickly stashes away for stealth-mode", "bullet_point3": "GMX IN-LINE MIXER - Balance your settings for game audio and voice chat", "bullet_point4": "EQ3 - Sound equalization settings for games, music and movies Bass Mode, Supreme Mode, and Precision Mode", "bullet_point5": "COMPATIBILITY - Compatible with Xbox 360, PS3, PS4 and PC as well as most mobile phones, tablets and MP3 players WIRED HEADSET - Not just for games, get more from your music with enhanced audio and attacking bass", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "Skullcandy", "item_name": "Skullcandy SLYR Gaming Headset, Blue (SMSLFY-012)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Got mine in April and one side stopped working this week -- I've only had them for 4 months.  Customer service has yet to respond.  I'm not impressed."}, {"answer_text": "No, its a good set for its price range."}, {"answer_text": "I still love this headset. I own 3 other turtle beach headsets. The only other I can recommend would be the X12 headset. It has good sound, just not as good, but it's cheaper, too."}, {"answer_text": "I bought it as a gift.  I have since heard that it is an awesome headset and performs better than others."}, {"answer_text": "No, this headset has not given me any problems, and when I show people, they usually ask me what kind it is. It's worth the 80"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx27G7PAA24UCVQ", "question_text": "Can someone help me figure out how to get the mic working on the head set with a xbox one. we have the adapter cord also.", "asin": "B01HD37D60", "bullet_point1": "1. Great sound quality and accurate sound pickup,over-ear headband with mic and convenient sound control knob,omnidirectional noise reduction microphone with flexible tube.", "bullet_point2": "2. Comfortable wearing and great noise cancelling, earmuffs are made of skin friendly leather material. Super soft over-ear pads and padded headset top that are more comfortable for long time wear. Earmuffs are well-padded, which also helps cut out background noise.", "bullet_point3": "3. Unique stylish and exquisite craftsmanship, multi-color crack breathing LED lights can highlight more feeling in the game world. Sturdy and durable braided cable can reduce external resistance, velcro cable tie to prevent line twining.", "bullet_point4": "4. Work for PC, computer, laptop, capable of various games, and need adapter to work for PS4, PS3, or Xbox 360.", "bullet_point5": "5. Note: There is a USB jack for powering the LED lights, and two audio connectors for the earpieces and the microphone. The green jack is for the headphones, and the red one is for the microphone.", "product_description": "Stimulate experience --- Inspire life    Combaterwing devotes to offering green,safe and perfect gaming fitting,for powerful sound field and realistic atmosphere of the game.   Comfortable supremacy: Earmuffs are made of skin friendly leather material, Super-soft ear cushions and cushion over the top of the headset.   High quality: High precision 50mm magnetic neodymium driver and sound source position,omnidirectional noise reduction microphone with flexible tube, built-in a volume controller and mic.     Specification:   Model: KOTION EACH G1000 Driver diameter: 50mm Impedance: 32ohm Sensitivity: 105dB +/- 3dB Frequency range: 20-20KHz Mic dimension: 6.0   5.0mm Mic sensitivity: -38dB +/- 3dB Mic impedance: 2.2kohm Directivity: Omnidirectional Led operating voltage: DC5V+/-5% Operating current: Below 100mA Headset interface: USB (plug the USB connector, LED light is on, unplug, it off) + 3.5mm stereo Cable length: Approx. 2.1m / 6.89ft LED light: Multi-color breathing light Headphone color: Black&red, Black&blue, Black&green Headphone size: Approx. 21   11   22cm / 8.3   4.3   8.7in Headphone weight: 339g / 12.0oz Package size: 20   11.8   22.8cm / 7.9   4.6   9.0in Package weight: 475g / 1.05Lbs     Package content:   1   KOTION EACH G1000 Headphone.     NOTE    The USB is ONLY FOR POWERING the LED in the headphones, not for sound or microphone use.   If you want this headset work on PS4, it will need a 3.5mm Stereo Jack Splitter Cable Adapter Connectors.", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "PC Gaming Headset, G1000 Professional 3.5mm Bass Stereo Headphones with Microphone LED Lighting for Computer Laptop and Smartphones (Green)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Hi J. Klenske, if your xbox one is the new version, you can just use with a normal 2 in 1 splitter cable. If your xbox one is the old version, then you have to buy a microsoft adapter to that it work."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1KQK3Q47BUOOT", "question_text": "Can it work onxbox 360 wireless??", "asin": "B01M26MCVN", "bullet_point1": "Bluetooth/Wired Gaming Headphones: B3506 is not only a Bluetooth headset, but also a wired headset. Compatible with many devices by connecting its included audio cable, such as for iPhone 6 / 6S Plus, Samsung S5, S4, LG, Xiaomi, iPad, PC, laptop, PlayStation 4, etc.  Note: This B3506 Bluetooth headset did work with PS4, but it works only through plugging into the PS4 dualshock controller by Line-in Cable rather than works via Bluetooth", "bullet_point2": "Bluetooth 4.1 Gaming Headsets: Adopted advanced Bluetooth 4.1 technology and fast pairing function, when high speed connecting, bring higher-quality stereo sound experience. Up to 10m/33ft of Range without obstacles when on music. Delivers deep bass, immersive sound at any volume, making them the best Bluetooth wireless headphones.", "bullet_point3": "Superior Battery Capacity: With 400mAh high capacity rechargeable build-in lithium battery, the wireless headphones last up to 8 hours playing time and 180 hours standby time. Effortless touch controls allow for simple command of your music and calls. Easily skip songs, change the volume and take calls right from the headphones.", "bullet_point4": "Enhanced Bass, HiFi Impact: Right bass can make a huge difference to the impact that any music can have. In addition, use of 40MM NdFeB strong magnet speakers enhance the bass horn shock effect and widen the sound field - thus it lets you play HIFI sound levels.", "bullet_point5": "Foldable Gaming Headset: It is portable designed, so that you can enjoy favorite tunes or games wherever and whenever you want, beach, outdoor, gym or anything else. Also, Its closed protein ear cushion blocks noise in almost any environment for better guaranteed comfort.", "product_description": "Main Features: KOTION EACH B3506 wired and wireless gaming headphones Support volume control, song switch In-line control with microphone, for hands-free calls Built-in 400mAh rechargeable Li-polymer battery, about 8h working time Three colors for options Brand: KOTION EACH  Model: B3506  Wearing type: Headband  Function: Answering Phone,Bluetooth,Microphone,Song Switching Headset type: Dynamic  Connectivity: Wired and Wireless  Connecting interface: AUX-IN,Micro USB  Application: Computer,Mobile phone,Portable Media Player  Driver unit: 40mm  Impedance: 32ohms  Working Time: 8h  Charging Time.: 3h  Compatible with: Computer Bluetooth: Yes  Bluetooth Version: V4.1  Bluetooth distance: W/O obstacles 10m  Bluetooth protocol: A2DP,AVRCP,HFP,HSP  Bluetooth mode: Hands free Battery Capacity(mAh): 400mAh Package weight: 0.435 kg  Product size (L x W x H): 18.00 x 8.50 x 20.00 cm / 7.09 x 3.35 x 7.87 inches  Package size (L x W x H): 14.50 x 9.00 x 18.50 cm / 5.71 x 3.54 x 7.28 inches Package Contents: 1 x Headphones, 1 x USB Cable, 1 x Audio Cable, 1 x Chinese / English User Manual", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Bluetooth Gaming Headset, Kotion Each B3506 V4.1 Wireless Foldable Gaming Headphones with Microphone for PC Computer PS4 iPhone iPad (Black Blue)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Sorry, it can not. it can work on ps4 with the attached cable line"}, {"answer_text": "No it does not."}]}
{"question_id": "TxBGODJ96QAA4N", "question_text": "I just bought these. and can i get them to snap on anywhere i've been trying for 10 minutes now. don't want to break anything.", "asin": "B081SWY8L2", "bullet_point1": "Note: Please adjust the hole of frame to avoid signal interference", "bullet_point2": "Features: Anti-break shock absorbing, anti-scratching, shatterproof and Anti-slip.", "bullet_point3": "Easy Installation: Lightweight, flexible, easy to snap on/off installation. If you don\u2019t know how to install it, please see the installation video and pictures in this product page", "bullet_point4": "Package Including: 2 X Protective Frame. Not including the Oculus Controllers", "bullet_point5": "Suggestion: Use silicone cover and controller skins with this shell, you could get much best gaming experience", "product_description": "Updated Version Protective Frame Collision Protective Shell for Oculus Quest & Oculus Rift S Features Features buffering shock absorbing anti-scratching shatterproof Anti-slip High quality material . Easy to install and take apart. Package Including:  2 X Protective Frame.  Not including the Oculus Controllers", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "1 Pair Anti Break Shell Protective Frame for Oculus Quest & Oculus Rift Controllers Collision Protection", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "You have to put the individual clips on first.  Then you can attach the outer ring by putting the begs into the holes on the clips."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2FIBVD0VG1JSD", "question_text": "Does this come with the adapter to get game sounds from the PS3?", "asin": "B07HJDZRJP", "bullet_point1": "REVAMPED 2020 COMFY DESIGN it's time for a high quality gaming headset without breaking the bank. TBI Pro has remastered and perfected what you always need in a gaming set: improved microphone, high quality sound, and exceptional comfort.", "bullet_point2": "PROFESSIONAL MICROPHONE AND VOLUME CONTROL super nice volume buttons and a dedicated mute button give an immense sense of control the one you need in your gaming adventures. With 50mm dynamic drivers and the noise canceling and steel beam slider, you can customize the headset with microphone to fit your face comfortably and completely turn yourself out of the surrounding sounds.", "bullet_point3": "UNIVERSAL GAMING HEADSET DESIGNED BY GAMERS these headphones can be used with your PC, Nintendo Switch, XboxOne headset or PS4 headset they work with any of the gaming consoles. Get the multiplatform for your maximum enjoyment with sound and microphone quality that will make your gaming even more impressive.", "bullet_point4": "HUGE 50MM DYNAMIC FOR REAL GAMING EXPERIENCE remastered for premium quality, superior comfort and ergonomics, the TBI Pro Gaming headset uses steel slider, premium leather headband and irresistibly soft, comfy and breathable earmuffs the durable comfort you deserve. The bright LED lights are also here for even better gaming effect.", "bullet_point5": "DESIGNED IN CHICAGO JOINTLY WITH GAMERS. Focus on the main gaming preferences and requirements in combination with advanced aulio technologies makes this gaming headset the best option for sophisticated gamers.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "TBI Pro", "item_name": "[Upgraded 2020] Gaming Headset IMBA V8 for 3D Surround Sound, PS4 Xbox One Headset   Noise Cancelling Mic Chat Headset, Over-Ear Gaming Headphones for PC, Xbox One, PS3, PS4, Nintendo Switch", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "If your controller has 3,5 mm porn no adapter will be needed"}, {"answer_text": "Yes, it does."}]}
{"question_id": "TxCTYK3YL7JU7", "question_text": "Can i just connect both the usb and headphone jack of the headset to my xbox instead of just my controller or just the usb can do that?", "asin": "B07HJDZRJP", "bullet_point1": "REVAMPED 2020 COMFY DESIGN it's time for a high quality gaming headset without breaking the bank. TBI Pro has remastered and perfected what you always need in a gaming set: improved microphone, high quality sound, and exceptional comfort.", "bullet_point2": "PROFESSIONAL MICROPHONE AND VOLUME CONTROL super nice volume buttons and a dedicated mute button give an immense sense of control the one you need in your gaming adventures. With 50mm dynamic drivers and the noise canceling and steel beam slider, you can customize the headset with microphone to fit your face comfortably and completely turn yourself out of the surrounding sounds.", "bullet_point3": "UNIVERSAL GAMING HEADSET DESIGNED BY GAMERS these headphones can be used with your PC, Nintendo Switch, XboxOne headset or PS4 headset they work with any of the gaming consoles. Get the multiplatform for your maximum enjoyment with sound and microphone quality that will make your gaming even more impressive.", "bullet_point4": "HUGE 50MM DYNAMIC FOR REAL GAMING EXPERIENCE remastered for premium quality, superior comfort and ergonomics, the TBI Pro Gaming headset uses steel slider, premium leather headband and irresistibly soft, comfy and breathable earmuffs the durable comfort you deserve. The bright LED lights are also here for even better gaming effect.", "bullet_point5": "DESIGNED IN CHICAGO JOINTLY WITH GAMERS. Focus on the main gaming preferences and requirements in combination with advanced aulio technologies makes this gaming headset the best option for sophisticated gamers.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "TBI Pro", "item_name": "[Upgraded 2020] Gaming Headset IMBA V8 for 3D Surround Sound, PS4 Xbox One Headset   Noise Cancelling Mic Chat Headset, Over-Ear Gaming Headphones for PC, Xbox One, PS3, PS4, Nintendo Switch", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yeah both the usb and headphone jack"}, {"answer_text": "Have yo connect Jack to controller with add on adapter. Won't work plugged directly to xbox. Go wireless   Turtle beach 600 . Much better"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2NGTP6WDR5LWM", "question_text": "The cable that connects the headset to the ps4, is fraying and haven\u2019t even had a year. can i buy just the cable and not purchase a new headset", "asin": "B07HJDZRJP", "bullet_point1": "REVAMPED 2020 COMFY DESIGN it's time for a high quality gaming headset without breaking the bank. TBI Pro has remastered and perfected what you always need in a gaming set: improved microphone, high quality sound, and exceptional comfort.", "bullet_point2": "PROFESSIONAL MICROPHONE AND VOLUME CONTROL super nice volume buttons and a dedicated mute button give an immense sense of control the one you need in your gaming adventures. With 50mm dynamic drivers and the noise canceling and steel beam slider, you can customize the headset with microphone to fit your face comfortably and completely turn yourself out of the surrounding sounds.", "bullet_point3": "UNIVERSAL GAMING HEADSET DESIGNED BY GAMERS these headphones can be used with your PC, Nintendo Switch, XboxOne headset or PS4 headset they work with any of the gaming consoles. Get the multiplatform for your maximum enjoyment with sound and microphone quality that will make your gaming even more impressive.", "bullet_point4": "HUGE 50MM DYNAMIC FOR REAL GAMING EXPERIENCE remastered for premium quality, superior comfort and ergonomics, the TBI Pro Gaming headset uses steel slider, premium leather headband and irresistibly soft, comfy and breathable earmuffs the durable comfort you deserve. The bright LED lights are also here for even better gaming effect.", "bullet_point5": "DESIGNED IN CHICAGO JOINTLY WITH GAMERS. Focus on the main gaming preferences and requirements in combination with advanced aulio technologies makes this gaming headset the best option for sophisticated gamers.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "TBI Pro", "item_name": "[Upgraded 2020] Gaming Headset IMBA V8 for 3D Surround Sound, PS4 Xbox One Headset   Noise Cancelling Mic Chat Headset, Over-Ear Gaming Headphones for PC, Xbox One, PS3, PS4, Nintendo Switch", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Did you try electrical tape, or cord is completely severed?"}, {"answer_text": "I dont believe so, i have had the same issue with two of these headsets previously. The first time i emailed the company and they replaced it for me but the second one i havent had replaced yet as it is still functioning at the moment"}, {"answer_text": "Contact the seller.  Their customer service is fantastic. I am sure they can help. They replaced my son's.  Actually they sent him a whole new headset."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3VEVWAJD4EVC7", "question_text": "can this set be used with only the usb port?", "asin": "B07HJDZRJP", "bullet_point1": "REVAMPED 2020 COMFY DESIGN it's time for a high quality gaming headset without breaking the bank. TBI Pro has remastered and perfected what you always need in a gaming set: improved microphone, high quality sound, and exceptional comfort.", "bullet_point2": "PROFESSIONAL MICROPHONE AND VOLUME CONTROL super nice volume buttons and a dedicated mute button give an immense sense of control the one you need in your gaming adventures. With 50mm dynamic drivers and the noise canceling and steel beam slider, you can customize the headset with microphone to fit your face comfortably and completely turn yourself out of the surrounding sounds.", "bullet_point3": "UNIVERSAL GAMING HEADSET DESIGNED BY GAMERS these headphones can be used with your PC, Nintendo Switch, XboxOne headset or PS4 headset they work with any of the gaming consoles. Get the multiplatform for your maximum enjoyment with sound and microphone quality that will make your gaming even more impressive.", "bullet_point4": "HUGE 50MM DYNAMIC FOR REAL GAMING EXPERIENCE remastered for premium quality, superior comfort and ergonomics, the TBI Pro Gaming headset uses steel slider, premium leather headband and irresistibly soft, comfy and breathable earmuffs the durable comfort you deserve. The bright LED lights are also here for even better gaming effect.", "bullet_point5": "DESIGNED IN CHICAGO JOINTLY WITH GAMERS. Focus on the main gaming preferences and requirements in combination with advanced aulio technologies makes this gaming headset the best option for sophisticated gamers.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "TBI Pro", "item_name": "[Upgraded 2020] Gaming Headset IMBA V8 for 3D Surround Sound, PS4 Xbox One Headset   Noise Cancelling Mic Chat Headset, Over-Ear Gaming Headphones for PC, Xbox One, PS3, PS4, Nintendo Switch", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No, USB only powers up LED light"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2INAJ5R67GM9F", "question_text": "Are headphones only good to talk with other gamers or can they be used if you want to hear the game volumn alone like a walkman?", "asin": "B07HJDZRJP", "bullet_point1": "REVAMPED 2020 COMFY DESIGN it's time for a high quality gaming headset without breaking the bank. TBI Pro has remastered and perfected what you always need in a gaming set: improved microphone, high quality sound, and exceptional comfort.", "bullet_point2": "PROFESSIONAL MICROPHONE AND VOLUME CONTROL super nice volume buttons and a dedicated mute button give an immense sense of control the one you need in your gaming adventures. With 50mm dynamic drivers and the noise canceling and steel beam slider, you can customize the headset with microphone to fit your face comfortably and completely turn yourself out of the surrounding sounds.", "bullet_point3": "UNIVERSAL GAMING HEADSET DESIGNED BY GAMERS these headphones can be used with your PC, Nintendo Switch, XboxOne headset or PS4 headset they work with any of the gaming consoles. Get the multiplatform for your maximum enjoyment with sound and microphone quality that will make your gaming even more impressive.", "bullet_point4": "HUGE 50MM DYNAMIC FOR REAL GAMING EXPERIENCE remastered for premium quality, superior comfort and ergonomics, the TBI Pro Gaming headset uses steel slider, premium leather headband and irresistibly soft, comfy and breathable earmuffs the durable comfort you deserve. The bright LED lights are also here for even better gaming effect.", "bullet_point5": "DESIGNED IN CHICAGO JOINTLY WITH GAMERS. Focus on the main gaming preferences and requirements in combination with advanced aulio technologies makes this gaming headset the best option for sophisticated gamers.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "TBI Pro", "item_name": "[Upgraded 2020] Gaming Headset IMBA V8 for 3D Surround Sound, PS4 Xbox One Headset   Noise Cancelling Mic Chat Headset, Over-Ear Gaming Headphones for PC, Xbox One, PS3, PS4, Nintendo Switch", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "These tangle very bad, do yourself a favor and get a decent pair of headphones."}, {"answer_text": "These earphone can be used for both purposes. They are fantastic."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3B3SLGN0FYCIM", "question_text": "Does the xbox one adapter make the audio quality better? currently i plug directly into controller and audio isn\u2019t very good.", "asin": "B07HJDZRJP", "bullet_point1": "REVAMPED 2020 COMFY DESIGN it's time for a high quality gaming headset without breaking the bank. TBI Pro has remastered and perfected what you always need in a gaming set: improved microphone, high quality sound, and exceptional comfort.", "bullet_point2": "PROFESSIONAL MICROPHONE AND VOLUME CONTROL super nice volume buttons and a dedicated mute button give an immense sense of control the one you need in your gaming adventures. With 50mm dynamic drivers and the noise canceling and steel beam slider, you can customize the headset with microphone to fit your face comfortably and completely turn yourself out of the surrounding sounds.", "bullet_point3": "UNIVERSAL GAMING HEADSET DESIGNED BY GAMERS these headphones can be used with your PC, Nintendo Switch, XboxOne headset or PS4 headset they work with any of the gaming consoles. Get the multiplatform for your maximum enjoyment with sound and microphone quality that will make your gaming even more impressive.", "bullet_point4": "HUGE 50MM DYNAMIC FOR REAL GAMING EXPERIENCE remastered for premium quality, superior comfort and ergonomics, the TBI Pro Gaming headset uses steel slider, premium leather headband and irresistibly soft, comfy and breathable earmuffs the durable comfort you deserve. The bright LED lights are also here for even better gaming effect.", "bullet_point5": "DESIGNED IN CHICAGO JOINTLY WITH GAMERS. Focus on the main gaming preferences and requirements in combination with advanced aulio technologies makes this gaming headset the best option for sophisticated gamers.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "TBI Pro", "item_name": "[Upgraded 2020] Gaming Headset IMBA V8 for 3D Surround Sound, PS4 Xbox One Headset   Noise Cancelling Mic Chat Headset, Over-Ear Gaming Headphones for PC, Xbox One, PS3, PS4, Nintendo Switch", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Sorry I do not have a Xbox one so i can't say"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1VZBKZD3JT2Z1", "question_text": "Do these have mic monitoring? Meaning you can hear your own voice through the headset?", "asin": "B07HJDZRJP", "bullet_point1": "REVAMPED 2020 COMFY DESIGN it's time for a high quality gaming headset without breaking the bank. TBI Pro has remastered and perfected what you always need in a gaming set: improved microphone, high quality sound, and exceptional comfort.", "bullet_point2": "PROFESSIONAL MICROPHONE AND VOLUME CONTROL super nice volume buttons and a dedicated mute button give an immense sense of control the one you need in your gaming adventures. With 50mm dynamic drivers and the noise canceling and steel beam slider, you can customize the headset with microphone to fit your face comfortably and completely turn yourself out of the surrounding sounds.", "bullet_point3": "UNIVERSAL GAMING HEADSET DESIGNED BY GAMERS these headphones can be used with your PC, Nintendo Switch, XboxOne headset or PS4 headset they work with any of the gaming consoles. Get the multiplatform for your maximum enjoyment with sound and microphone quality that will make your gaming even more impressive.", "bullet_point4": "HUGE 50MM DYNAMIC FOR REAL GAMING EXPERIENCE remastered for premium quality, superior comfort and ergonomics, the TBI Pro Gaming headset uses steel slider, premium leather headband and irresistibly soft, comfy and breathable earmuffs the durable comfort you deserve. The bright LED lights are also here for even better gaming effect.", "bullet_point5": "DESIGNED IN CHICAGO JOINTLY WITH GAMERS. Focus on the main gaming preferences and requirements in combination with advanced aulio technologies makes this gaming headset the best option for sophisticated gamers.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "TBI Pro", "item_name": "[Upgraded 2020] Gaming Headset IMBA V8 for 3D Surround Sound, PS4 Xbox One Headset   Noise Cancelling Mic Chat Headset, Over-Ear Gaming Headphones for PC, Xbox One, PS3, PS4, Nintendo Switch", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "No, unfortunately they do not.. I too love that feature but its not available with these."}, {"answer_text": "you can set mic monitoring i game settings"}, {"answer_text": "My son says no."}, {"answer_text": "No you cannot hear your own voice"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2RSGCPMN9RBBF", "question_text": "Is it 2019 yet?", "asin": "B07HJDZRJP", "bullet_point1": "REVAMPED 2020 COMFY DESIGN it's time for a high quality gaming headset without breaking the bank. TBI Pro has remastered and perfected what you always need in a gaming set: improved microphone, high quality sound, and exceptional comfort.", "bullet_point2": "PROFESSIONAL MICROPHONE AND VOLUME CONTROL super nice volume buttons and a dedicated mute button give an immense sense of control the one you need in your gaming adventures. With 50mm dynamic drivers and the noise canceling and steel beam slider, you can customize the headset with microphone to fit your face comfortably and completely turn yourself out of the surrounding sounds.", "bullet_point3": "UNIVERSAL GAMING HEADSET DESIGNED BY GAMERS these headphones can be used with your PC, Nintendo Switch, XboxOne headset or PS4 headset they work with any of the gaming consoles. Get the multiplatform for your maximum enjoyment with sound and microphone quality that will make your gaming even more impressive.", "bullet_point4": "HUGE 50MM DYNAMIC FOR REAL GAMING EXPERIENCE remastered for premium quality, superior comfort and ergonomics, the TBI Pro Gaming headset uses steel slider, premium leather headband and irresistibly soft, comfy and breathable earmuffs the durable comfort you deserve. The bright LED lights are also here for even better gaming effect.", "bullet_point5": "DESIGNED IN CHICAGO JOINTLY WITH GAMERS. Focus on the main gaming preferences and requirements in combination with advanced aulio technologies makes this gaming headset the best option for sophisticated gamers.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "TBI Pro", "item_name": "[Upgraded 2020] Gaming Headset IMBA V8 for 3D Surround Sound, PS4 Xbox One Headset   Noise Cancelling Mic Chat Headset, Over-Ear Gaming Headphones for PC, Xbox One, PS3, PS4, Nintendo Switch", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Yes."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1NHFZO2GFIYOD", "question_text": "Does this work for a switch ?", "asin": "B07HJDZRJP", "bullet_point1": "REVAMPED 2020 COMFY DESIGN it's time for a high quality gaming headset without breaking the bank. TBI Pro has remastered and perfected what you always need in a gaming set: improved microphone, high quality sound, and exceptional comfort.", "bullet_point2": "PROFESSIONAL MICROPHONE AND VOLUME CONTROL super nice volume buttons and a dedicated mute button give an immense sense of control the one you need in your gaming adventures. With 50mm dynamic drivers and the noise canceling and steel beam slider, you can customize the headset with microphone to fit your face comfortably and completely turn yourself out of the surrounding sounds.", "bullet_point3": "UNIVERSAL GAMING HEADSET DESIGNED BY GAMERS these headphones can be used with your PC, Nintendo Switch, XboxOne headset or PS4 headset they work with any of the gaming consoles. Get the multiplatform for your maximum enjoyment with sound and microphone quality that will make your gaming even more impressive.", "bullet_point4": "HUGE 50MM DYNAMIC FOR REAL GAMING EXPERIENCE remastered for premium quality, superior comfort and ergonomics, the TBI Pro Gaming headset uses steel slider, premium leather headband and irresistibly soft, comfy and breathable earmuffs the durable comfort you deserve. The bright LED lights are also here for even better gaming effect.", "bullet_point5": "DESIGNED IN CHICAGO JOINTLY WITH GAMERS. Focus on the main gaming preferences and requirements in combination with advanced aulio technologies makes this gaming headset the best option for sophisticated gamers.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "TBI Pro", "item_name": "[Upgraded 2020] Gaming Headset IMBA V8 for 3D Surround Sound, PS4 Xbox One Headset   Noise Cancelling Mic Chat Headset, Over-Ear Gaming Headphones for PC, Xbox One, PS3, PS4, Nintendo Switch", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Don\u2019t waste your money. I bought it and after 30 the mic stopped working and one side oh the headset stopped as well."}]}
{"question_id": "TxJFHZRDUY1TJY", "question_text": "does it work with a nintendo switch?", "asin": "B07HJDZRJP", "bullet_point1": "REVAMPED 2020 COMFY DESIGN it's time for a high quality gaming headset without breaking the bank. TBI Pro has remastered and perfected what you always need in a gaming set: improved microphone, high quality sound, and exceptional comfort.", "bullet_point2": "PROFESSIONAL MICROPHONE AND VOLUME CONTROL super nice volume buttons and a dedicated mute button give an immense sense of control the one you need in your gaming adventures. With 50mm dynamic drivers and the noise canceling and steel beam slider, you can customize the headset with microphone to fit your face comfortably and completely turn yourself out of the surrounding sounds.", "bullet_point3": "UNIVERSAL GAMING HEADSET DESIGNED BY GAMERS these headphones can be used with your PC, Nintendo Switch, XboxOne headset or PS4 headset they work with any of the gaming consoles. Get the multiplatform for your maximum enjoyment with sound and microphone quality that will make your gaming even more impressive.", "bullet_point4": "HUGE 50MM DYNAMIC FOR REAL GAMING EXPERIENCE remastered for premium quality, superior comfort and ergonomics, the TBI Pro Gaming headset uses steel slider, premium leather headband and irresistibly soft, comfy and breathable earmuffs the durable comfort you deserve. The bright LED lights are also here for even better gaming effect.", "bullet_point5": "DESIGNED IN CHICAGO JOINTLY WITH GAMERS. Focus on the main gaming preferences and requirements in combination with advanced aulio technologies makes this gaming headset the best option for sophisticated gamers.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "TBI Pro", "item_name": "[Upgraded 2020] Gaming Headset IMBA V8 for 3D Surround Sound, PS4 Xbox One Headset   Noise Cancelling Mic Chat Headset, Over-Ear Gaming Headphones for PC, Xbox One, PS3, PS4, Nintendo Switch", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Not sure don\u2019t own 1   Sorry"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2GDUESMAYBC0C", "question_text": "Do I need to buy anything extra to used in xbox one s controller?", "asin": "B07HJDZRJP", "bullet_point1": "REVAMPED 2020 COMFY DESIGN it's time for a high quality gaming headset without breaking the bank. TBI Pro has remastered and perfected what you always need in a gaming set: improved microphone, high quality sound, and exceptional comfort.", "bullet_point2": "PROFESSIONAL MICROPHONE AND VOLUME CONTROL super nice volume buttons and a dedicated mute button give an immense sense of control the one you need in your gaming adventures. With 50mm dynamic drivers and the noise canceling and steel beam slider, you can customize the headset with microphone to fit your face comfortably and completely turn yourself out of the surrounding sounds.", "bullet_point3": "UNIVERSAL GAMING HEADSET DESIGNED BY GAMERS these headphones can be used with your PC, Nintendo Switch, XboxOne headset or PS4 headset they work with any of the gaming consoles. Get the multiplatform for your maximum enjoyment with sound and microphone quality that will make your gaming even more impressive.", "bullet_point4": "HUGE 50MM DYNAMIC FOR REAL GAMING EXPERIENCE remastered for premium quality, superior comfort and ergonomics, the TBI Pro Gaming headset uses steel slider, premium leather headband and irresistibly soft, comfy and breathable earmuffs the durable comfort you deserve. The bright LED lights are also here for even better gaming effect.", "bullet_point5": "DESIGNED IN CHICAGO JOINTLY WITH GAMERS. Focus on the main gaming preferences and requirements in combination with advanced aulio technologies makes this gaming headset the best option for sophisticated gamers.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "TBI Pro", "item_name": "[Upgraded 2020] Gaming Headset IMBA V8 for 3D Surround Sound, PS4 Xbox One Headset   Noise Cancelling Mic Chat Headset, Over-Ear Gaming Headphones for PC, Xbox One, PS3, PS4, Nintendo Switch", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "One should not need any extra attachments to connect to an Xbox One S controller. As long as there is a 3.5 mm jack in the side of the controller facing one using it, you\u2019re good."}, {"answer_text": "If your controller has 3,5 mm jack port than you dont need to by adapter"}, {"answer_text": "No."}]}
{"question_id": "TxJQ477POPFN23", "question_text": "Does this gaming headset come with an adapter?", "asin": "B07V5Y53BG", "bullet_point1": "MULTIPLATFORM COMPATIBILITY This gaming headset with 3.5-millimeter audio jack, and attached with a extra splitter cable. It can be better compatible with PlayStation 4, PSP, Nintendo New 3DS LL/3DS (audio), Nintendo 3DS LL/3DS (audio),PC, Laptop, Tablet, Computer, Mobile Phone, Xbox one ( NOTE: the old version one need an extra Microsoft Adapter, not Included) and other devices that support a 3.5mm wired audio connection.", "bullet_point2": "3D SURROUND SOUND To put you in the center of the action. Playing a video game with headphones on is where sound in entertainment can have a realistic 3D effect, the sound seems to come from the outside world, not from inside the headphones. High precision 50mm drivers is perfect for GTA5, Metal Gear Solid, Call of Duty, Star Wars Battlefront 2015, Battlefield 1, World of Warcraft Legion, God of war etc.", "bullet_point3": "NOISE-CANCELING MICROPHONE As one of the best microphone in gaming, its retractable microphone can be adjusted to any angle you need. It can delivers crystal clear communication with friends and teammates better, and exceptional background noise cancellation. This noise-canceling microphone with flip-to-mute function, easily detaches when you want to listen to music or videos between games.", "bullet_point4": "MAX DURABLITY AND COMFORT DESIGN A sleek metal headband with a adjustable suspended pad and memory-foam earcups provide comfortable, stable fit. Vented earcups reduce listening fatigue during intense training sessions and blocking out external noise and improving bass response. Feature convenient controls for LED effects, mic mute, power, and volume, you can play for hours without fatigue or overheating.", "bullet_point5": "ATTENTIONS AND WARRANTY GUARANTEED Please note that if the cable is fully inserted and the switch is already on before use, the volume can be adjusted and make sure your devices are suitable for our combination of audio and voice connetors. In order to ensure the rights of customers, from the day of purchase of gaming headset, we offer 12 months warranty to our customer.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Mifanstech V-10 Gaming Headset for Xbox One Playstation 2 PS4 PC - 3.5mm Surround Sound, Noise Reduction Game Headphone with Microphone and Volume Control for Laptop, Tablet,Switch Games (Black)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "This xbox one headset can be better compatible with PlayStation 4, PSP, Nintendo New 3DS LL/3DS (audio), Nintendo 3DS LL/3DS (audio),PC, Laptop, Tablet, Computer, Mobile Phone, Xbox one ( NOTE: the old version one need an extra Microsoft Adapter, not Included) and other devices that support a 3.5mm wired audio connection."}]}
{"question_id": "TxQW9BTMP6KNKO", "question_text": "We can not get the mic or headset to work with pc!  What are we doing wrong?", "asin": "B07V5Y53BG", "bullet_point1": "MULTIPLATFORM COMPATIBILITY This gaming headset with 3.5-millimeter audio jack, and attached with a extra splitter cable. It can be better compatible with PlayStation 4, PSP, Nintendo New 3DS LL/3DS (audio), Nintendo 3DS LL/3DS (audio),PC, Laptop, Tablet, Computer, Mobile Phone, Xbox one ( NOTE: the old version one need an extra Microsoft Adapter, not Included) and other devices that support a 3.5mm wired audio connection.", "bullet_point2": "3D SURROUND SOUND To put you in the center of the action. Playing a video game with headphones on is where sound in entertainment can have a realistic 3D effect, the sound seems to come from the outside world, not from inside the headphones. High precision 50mm drivers is perfect for GTA5, Metal Gear Solid, Call of Duty, Star Wars Battlefront 2015, Battlefield 1, World of Warcraft Legion, God of war etc.", "bullet_point3": "NOISE-CANCELING MICROPHONE As one of the best microphone in gaming, its retractable microphone can be adjusted to any angle you need. It can delivers crystal clear communication with friends and teammates better, and exceptional background noise cancellation. This noise-canceling microphone with flip-to-mute function, easily detaches when you want to listen to music or videos between games.", "bullet_point4": "MAX DURABLITY AND COMFORT DESIGN A sleek metal headband with a adjustable suspended pad and memory-foam earcups provide comfortable, stable fit. Vented earcups reduce listening fatigue during intense training sessions and blocking out external noise and improving bass response. Feature convenient controls for LED effects, mic mute, power, and volume, you can play for hours without fatigue or overheating.", "bullet_point5": "ATTENTIONS AND WARRANTY GUARANTEED Please note that if the cable is fully inserted and the switch is already on before use, the volume can be adjusted and make sure your devices are suitable for our combination of audio and voice connetors. In order to ensure the rights of customers, from the day of purchase of gaming headset, we offer 12 months warranty to our customer.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Mifanstech V-10 Gaming Headset for Xbox One Playstation 2 PS4 PC - 3.5mm Surround Sound, Noise Reduction Game Headphone with Microphone and Volume Control for Laptop, Tablet,Switch Games (Black)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "If you have windows 10 you have to activate the mic for Cortana so you can talk to the PC. It was a little struggle but use the help section"}]}
{"question_id": "TxGX2E4OODJCU3", "question_text": "Do these work on a laptop? With only one 3.5 port", "asin": "B07V5Y53BG", "bullet_point1": "MULTIPLATFORM COMPATIBILITY This gaming headset with 3.5-millimeter audio jack, and attached with a extra splitter cable. It can be better compatible with PlayStation 4, PSP, Nintendo New 3DS LL/3DS (audio), Nintendo 3DS LL/3DS (audio),PC, Laptop, Tablet, Computer, Mobile Phone, Xbox one ( NOTE: the old version one need an extra Microsoft Adapter, not Included) and other devices that support a 3.5mm wired audio connection.", "bullet_point2": "3D SURROUND SOUND To put you in the center of the action. Playing a video game with headphones on is where sound in entertainment can have a realistic 3D effect, the sound seems to come from the outside world, not from inside the headphones. High precision 50mm drivers is perfect for GTA5, Metal Gear Solid, Call of Duty, Star Wars Battlefront 2015, Battlefield 1, World of Warcraft Legion, God of war etc.", "bullet_point3": "NOISE-CANCELING MICROPHONE As one of the best microphone in gaming, its retractable microphone can be adjusted to any angle you need. It can delivers crystal clear communication with friends and teammates better, and exceptional background noise cancellation. This noise-canceling microphone with flip-to-mute function, easily detaches when you want to listen to music or videos between games.", "bullet_point4": "MAX DURABLITY AND COMFORT DESIGN A sleek metal headband with a adjustable suspended pad and memory-foam earcups provide comfortable, stable fit. Vented earcups reduce listening fatigue during intense training sessions and blocking out external noise and improving bass response. Feature convenient controls for LED effects, mic mute, power, and volume, you can play for hours without fatigue or overheating.", "bullet_point5": "ATTENTIONS AND WARRANTY GUARANTEED Please note that if the cable is fully inserted and the switch is already on before use, the volume can be adjusted and make sure your devices are suitable for our combination of audio and voice connetors. In order to ensure the rights of customers, from the day of purchase of gaming headset, we offer 12 months warranty to our customer.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Mifanstech V-10 Gaming Headset for Xbox One Playstation 2 PS4 PC - 3.5mm Surround Sound, Noise Reduction Game Headphone with Microphone and Volume Control for Laptop, Tablet,Switch Games (Black)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Theres 2 ways use them theres 2 plugs put adapters u can use USB port or regular headphones port these are so awsome I love them"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx2DTR4NE48WIYZ", "question_text": "Can't get my Acer laptop to recognize that the mic even exists  not appearing in any control panel dropdowns. Any ideas?", "asin": "B07V5Y53BG", "bullet_point1": "MULTIPLATFORM COMPATIBILITY This gaming headset with 3.5-millimeter audio jack, and attached with a extra splitter cable. It can be better compatible with PlayStation 4, PSP, Nintendo New 3DS LL/3DS (audio), Nintendo 3DS LL/3DS (audio),PC, Laptop, Tablet, Computer, Mobile Phone, Xbox one ( NOTE: the old version one need an extra Microsoft Adapter, not Included) and other devices that support a 3.5mm wired audio connection.", "bullet_point2": "3D SURROUND SOUND To put you in the center of the action. Playing a video game with headphones on is where sound in entertainment can have a realistic 3D effect, the sound seems to come from the outside world, not from inside the headphones. High precision 50mm drivers is perfect for GTA5, Metal Gear Solid, Call of Duty, Star Wars Battlefront 2015, Battlefield 1, World of Warcraft Legion, God of war etc.", "bullet_point3": "NOISE-CANCELING MICROPHONE As one of the best microphone in gaming, its retractable microphone can be adjusted to any angle you need. It can delivers crystal clear communication with friends and teammates better, and exceptional background noise cancellation. This noise-canceling microphone with flip-to-mute function, easily detaches when you want to listen to music or videos between games.", "bullet_point4": "MAX DURABLITY AND COMFORT DESIGN A sleek metal headband with a adjustable suspended pad and memory-foam earcups provide comfortable, stable fit. Vented earcups reduce listening fatigue during intense training sessions and blocking out external noise and improving bass response. Feature convenient controls for LED effects, mic mute, power, and volume, you can play for hours without fatigue or overheating.", "bullet_point5": "ATTENTIONS AND WARRANTY GUARANTEED Please note that if the cable is fully inserted and the switch is already on before use, the volume can be adjusted and make sure your devices are suitable for our combination of audio and voice connetors. In order to ensure the rights of customers, from the day of purchase of gaming headset, we offer 12 months warranty to our customer.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Mifanstech V-10 Gaming Headset for Xbox One Playstation 2 PS4 PC - 3.5mm Surround Sound, Noise Reduction Game Headphone with Microphone and Volume Control for Laptop, Tablet,Switch Games (Black)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "Try using a headset/earphones with a mic. On some laptops- the mic isnt recognized or you cannot see it in any drop dowms- but if you plug into it with headphones/earbuds with a mic- it works just fine. Found that out during the current teleworking situation."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3959DB7T808P1", "question_text": "Does the gaming headset have any warranty?", "asin": "B07V5Y53BG", "bullet_point1": "MULTIPLATFORM COMPATIBILITY This gaming headset with 3.5-millimeter audio jack, and attached with a extra splitter cable. It can be better compatible with PlayStation 4, PSP, Nintendo New 3DS LL/3DS (audio), Nintendo 3DS LL/3DS (audio),PC, Laptop, Tablet, Computer, Mobile Phone, Xbox one ( NOTE: the old version one need an extra Microsoft Adapter, not Included) and other devices that support a 3.5mm wired audio connection.", "bullet_point2": "3D SURROUND SOUND To put you in the center of the action. Playing a video game with headphones on is where sound in entertainment can have a realistic 3D effect, the sound seems to come from the outside world, not from inside the headphones. High precision 50mm drivers is perfect for GTA5, Metal Gear Solid, Call of Duty, Star Wars Battlefront 2015, Battlefield 1, World of Warcraft Legion, God of war etc.", "bullet_point3": "NOISE-CANCELING MICROPHONE As one of the best microphone in gaming, its retractable microphone can be adjusted to any angle you need. It can delivers crystal clear communication with friends and teammates better, and exceptional background noise cancellation. This noise-canceling microphone with flip-to-mute function, easily detaches when you want to listen to music or videos between games.", "bullet_point4": "MAX DURABLITY AND COMFORT DESIGN A sleek metal headband with a adjustable suspended pad and memory-foam earcups provide comfortable, stable fit. Vented earcups reduce listening fatigue during intense training sessions and blocking out external noise and improving bass response. Feature convenient controls for LED effects, mic mute, power, and volume, you can play for hours without fatigue or overheating.", "bullet_point5": "ATTENTIONS AND WARRANTY GUARANTEED Please note that if the cable is fully inserted and the switch is already on before use, the volume can be adjusted and make sure your devices are suitable for our combination of audio and voice connetors. In order to ensure the rights of customers, from the day of purchase of gaming headset, we offer 12 months warranty to our customer.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Mifanstech V-10 Gaming Headset for Xbox One Playstation 2 PS4 PC - 3.5mm Surround Sound, Noise Reduction Game Headphone with Microphone and Volume Control for Laptop, Tablet,Switch Games (Black)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "yes", "answers": [{"answer_text": "YES. Please contact the seller with any problems about the ps4 headset. The company will provide 12 months of free replacement, or even a full refund for your xbox one headset."}]}
{"question_id": "Tx1IKTM0KZ801DC", "question_text": "I'm very interested in this headphones, but the shipping for Serbia is very expens, 77$. Can you send me this headphones some other way to cost less?", "asin": "B07V5Y53BG", "bullet_point1": "MULTIPLATFORM COMPATIBILITY This gaming headset with 3.5-millimeter audio jack, and attached with a extra splitter cable. It can be better compatible with PlayStation 4, PSP, Nintendo New 3DS LL/3DS (audio), Nintendo 3DS LL/3DS (audio),PC, Laptop, Tablet, Computer, Mobile Phone, Xbox one ( NOTE: the old version one need an extra Microsoft Adapter, not Included) and other devices that support a 3.5mm wired audio connection.", "bullet_point2": "3D SURROUND SOUND To put you in the center of the action. Playing a video game with headphones on is where sound in entertainment can have a realistic 3D effect, the sound seems to come from the outside world, not from inside the headphones. High precision 50mm drivers is perfect for GTA5, Metal Gear Solid, Call of Duty, Star Wars Battlefront 2015, Battlefield 1, World of Warcraft Legion, God of war etc.", "bullet_point3": "NOISE-CANCELING MICROPHONE As one of the best microphone in gaming, its retractable microphone can be adjusted to any angle you need. It can delivers crystal clear communication with friends and teammates better, and exceptional background noise cancellation. This noise-canceling microphone with flip-to-mute function, easily detaches when you want to listen to music or videos between games.", "bullet_point4": "MAX DURABLITY AND COMFORT DESIGN A sleek metal headband with a adjustable suspended pad and memory-foam earcups provide comfortable, stable fit. Vented earcups reduce listening fatigue during intense training sessions and blocking out external noise and improving bass response. Feature convenient controls for LED effects, mic mute, power, and volume, you can play for hours without fatigue or overheating.", "bullet_point5": "ATTENTIONS AND WARRANTY GUARANTEED Please note that if the cable is fully inserted and the switch is already on before use, the volume can be adjusted and make sure your devices are suitable for our combination of audio and voice connetors. In order to ensure the rights of customers, from the day of purchase of gaming headset, we offer 12 months warranty to our customer.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Mifanstech V-10 Gaming Headset for Xbox One Playstation 2 PS4 PC - 3.5mm Surround Sound, Noise Reduction Game Headphone with Microphone and Volume Control for Laptop, Tablet,Switch Games (Black)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "neutral", "answers": [{"answer_text": "This is a great product. It'll be worth the extra cost"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx280JM3F99UCFK", "question_text": "Are the ear cups leather or leatherette?", "asin": "B07V5Y53BG", "bullet_point1": "MULTIPLATFORM COMPATIBILITY This gaming headset with 3.5-millimeter audio jack, and attached with a extra splitter cable. It can be better compatible with PlayStation 4, PSP, Nintendo New 3DS LL/3DS (audio), Nintendo 3DS LL/3DS (audio),PC, Laptop, Tablet, Computer, Mobile Phone, Xbox one ( NOTE: the old version one need an extra Microsoft Adapter, not Included) and other devices that support a 3.5mm wired audio connection.", "bullet_point2": "3D SURROUND SOUND To put you in the center of the action. Playing a video game with headphones on is where sound in entertainment can have a realistic 3D effect, the sound seems to come from the outside world, not from inside the headphones. High precision 50mm drivers is perfect for GTA5, Metal Gear Solid, Call of Duty, Star Wars Battlefront 2015, Battlefield 1, World of Warcraft Legion, God of war etc.", "bullet_point3": "NOISE-CANCELING MICROPHONE As one of the best microphone in gaming, its retractable microphone can be adjusted to any angle you need. It can delivers crystal clear communication with friends and teammates better, and exceptional background noise cancellation. This noise-canceling microphone with flip-to-mute function, easily detaches when you want to listen to music or videos between games.", "bullet_point4": "MAX DURABLITY AND COMFORT DESIGN A sleek metal headband with a adjustable suspended pad and memory-foam earcups provide comfortable, stable fit. Vented earcups reduce listening fatigue during intense training sessions and blocking out external noise and improving bass response. Feature convenient controls for LED effects, mic mute, power, and volume, you can play for hours without fatigue or overheating.", "bullet_point5": "ATTENTIONS AND WARRANTY GUARANTEED Please note that if the cable is fully inserted and the switch is already on before use, the volume can be adjusted and make sure your devices are suitable for our combination of audio and voice connetors. In order to ensure the rights of customers, from the day of purchase of gaming headset, we offer 12 months warranty to our customer.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Mifanstech V-10 Gaming Headset for Xbox One Playstation 2 PS4 PC - 3.5mm Surround Sound, Noise Reduction Game Headphone with Microphone and Volume Control for Laptop, Tablet,Switch Games (Black)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "They aren\u2019t real leather, however, they are comfortable"}, {"answer_text": "Leatherette"}, {"answer_text": "Leatherette memory foam"}, {"answer_text": "Leatherette"}]}
{"question_id": "Tx3D47IYYD3PA2S", "question_text": "Why doesn\u2019t it light up when I\u2019m using it for the Xbox?", "asin": "B07V5Y53BG", "bullet_point1": "MULTIPLATFORM COMPATIBILITY This gaming headset with 3.5-millimeter audio jack, and attached with a extra splitter cable. It can be better compatible with PlayStation 4, PSP, Nintendo New 3DS LL/3DS (audio), Nintendo 3DS LL/3DS (audio),PC, Laptop, Tablet, Computer, Mobile Phone, Xbox one ( NOTE: the old version one need an extra Microsoft Adapter, not Included) and other devices that support a 3.5mm wired audio connection.", "bullet_point2": "3D SURROUND SOUND To put you in the center of the action. Playing a video game with headphones on is where sound in entertainment can have a realistic 3D effect, the sound seems to come from the outside world, not from inside the headphones. High precision 50mm drivers is perfect for GTA5, Metal Gear Solid, Call of Duty, Star Wars Battlefront 2015, Battlefield 1, World of Warcraft Legion, God of war etc.", "bullet_point3": "NOISE-CANCELING MICROPHONE As one of the best microphone in gaming, its retractable microphone can be adjusted to any angle you need. It can delivers crystal clear communication with friends and teammates better, and exceptional background noise cancellation. This noise-canceling microphone with flip-to-mute function, easily detaches when you want to listen to music or videos between games.", "bullet_point4": "MAX DURABLITY AND COMFORT DESIGN A sleek metal headband with a adjustable suspended pad and memory-foam earcups provide comfortable, stable fit. Vented earcups reduce listening fatigue during intense training sessions and blocking out external noise and improving bass response. Feature convenient controls for LED effects, mic mute, power, and volume, you can play for hours without fatigue or overheating.", "bullet_point5": "ATTENTIONS AND WARRANTY GUARANTEED Please note that if the cable is fully inserted and the switch is already on before use, the volume can be adjusted and make sure your devices are suitable for our combination of audio and voice connetors. In order to ensure the rights of customers, from the day of purchase of gaming headset, we offer 12 months warranty to our customer.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Mifanstech V-10 Gaming Headset for Xbox One Playstation 2 PS4 PC - 3.5mm Surround Sound, Noise Reduction Game Headphone with Microphone and Volume Control for Laptop, Tablet,Switch Games (Black)", "question_type": "WH", "answer_aggregated": "N/A", "answers": [{"answer_text": "The USB has to be plugged in for the lights to come on. They do make an adapter for your controller you can buy."}]}
{"question_id": "TxTZ7ZT6HVWWFE", "question_text": "Are these open back headphones? Doesn't look like it.", "asin": "B07V5Y53BG", "bullet_point1": "MULTIPLATFORM COMPATIBILITY This gaming headset with 3.5-millimeter audio jack, and attached with a extra splitter cable. It can be better compatible with PlayStation 4, PSP, Nintendo New 3DS LL/3DS (audio), Nintendo 3DS LL/3DS (audio),PC, Laptop, Tablet, Computer, Mobile Phone, Xbox one ( NOTE: the old version one need an extra Microsoft Adapter, not Included) and other devices that support a 3.5mm wired audio connection.", "bullet_point2": "3D SURROUND SOUND To put you in the center of the action. Playing a video game with headphones on is where sound in entertainment can have a realistic 3D effect, the sound seems to come from the outside world, not from inside the headphones. High precision 50mm drivers is perfect for GTA5, Metal Gear Solid, Call of Duty, Star Wars Battlefront 2015, Battlefield 1, World of Warcraft Legion, God of war etc.", "bullet_point3": "NOISE-CANCELING MICROPHONE As one of the best microphone in gaming, its retractable microphone can be adjusted to any angle you need. It can delivers crystal clear communication with friends and teammates better, and exceptional background noise cancellation. This noise-canceling microphone with flip-to-mute function, easily detaches when you want to listen to music or videos between games.", "bullet_point4": "MAX DURABLITY AND COMFORT DESIGN A sleek metal headband with a adjustable suspended pad and memory-foam earcups provide comfortable, stable fit. Vented earcups reduce listening fatigue during intense training sessions and blocking out external noise and improving bass response. Feature convenient controls for LED effects, mic mute, power, and volume, you can play for hours without fatigue or overheating.", "bullet_point5": "ATTENTIONS AND WARRANTY GUARANTEED Please note that if the cable is fully inserted and the switch is already on before use, the volume can be adjusted and make sure your devices are suitable for our combination of audio and voice connetors. In order to ensure the rights of customers, from the day of purchase of gaming headset, we offer 12 months warranty to our customer.", "product_description": "", "brand_name": "", "item_name": "Mifanstech V-10 Gaming Headset for Xbox One Playstation 2 PS4 PC - 3.5mm Surround Sound, Noise Reduction Game Headphone with Microphone and Volume Control for Laptop, Tablet,Switch Games (Black)", "question_type": "yes-no", "answer_aggregated": "no", "answers": [{"answer_text": "They are not"}]}
